<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>MouseGuests</title>
    <link>http://www.mouseguests.com</link>
    <description>Sharing our Disney obsession!</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2016 16:54:56 GMT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>mouseguests@habuma.com</dc:creator>
    <dc:date>2016-03-03T16:54:56Z</dc:date>
    <dc:language>en-US</dc:language>
    <item>
      <title>A few introductions are in order</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/05/A-few-introductions-are-in-order.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;After setting up this blog in December, we hopped on a plane and went to Disney World for a week. Then with the holidays and other activities consuming our time, we’re just now getting around to writing our first real blog post. As is customary, we’ll start by introducing ourselves and telling you a bit about how we became obsessed with Disney World and Disneyland.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;My name is Craig and I’ll probably be the one writing most of the articles here. Raymie is my beautiful and amazing wife and she is largely responsible for our Disney obsession. When we got married back in 1998, I asked her where she’d like to go on our honeymoon and she said Disney World. Neither of us had ever been before, so why not? I took care of the plans and booked us a week at Disney’s Dixie Landings Resort (now known as Port Orleans Riverside). It was an amazing trip! Even so, it’d be 10 years before we’d return…​&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Fast forward to 2008. By this time we had added Maisy and Madi, our two little princesses, to our family and decided to take them to Disney World. Maisy was 4 years old and Madi was 2. These ages were perfect for introducing them to Disney World and it was fun seeing it through their eyes. Of course, they were limited on what they could ride, so we spent a great deal of our time seeking out characters for photographs and autographs. Madi specifically wanted to meet Snow White so we went &lt;strong&gt;everywhere&lt;/strong&gt; to find her. Sadly we never found her. But it was a great trip nonetheless.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Three years passed before our next trip. By fall of 2011, Maisy had started figure skating and was invited to compete in a national figure skating competition in San Diego. While we were in California, we decided to drive up to Anaheim and visit Disneyland for our very first time. At that time construction walls were still up in California Adventure for Carthay Circle and Cars Land, but still had tons of fun. I recall finding Disneyland Park to have a lot of charm and character as compared to the Magic Kingdom, even if smaller.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;At this point our Disney obsession kicked into high gear with several trips in a row. I won’t bore you with mini trip reports for each trip, but here’s a summary of all of the Disney vacations we’ve taken thus far:&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="ulist"&gt; 
 &lt;ul&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dec 1998 : Walt Disney World (Dixie Landings)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dec 2008 : Walt Disney World (Caribbean Beach Resort)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;Aug 2011 : Disneyland (Good Neighbor Hotel)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dec 2012 : Walt Disney World (Port Orleans Riverside)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;Sep 2013 : Disneyland (Paradise Pier Hotel)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dec 2013 : Walt Disney World (Port Orleans Riverside)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;May 2014 : Walt Disney World (Port Orleans Riverside)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;Jan 2015 : Walt Disney World (Art of Animation)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;May 2015 : Disneyland (Grand Californian)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dec 2015 : Walt Disney World (Beach Club)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;/ul&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;We’re already planning for trips to Disney World this May and Disneyland in June. And we’ve even started talking about taking a Disney Cruise!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Suffice it to say, we’re obsessed. Along the way, I started posting to &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/MouseGuests"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/mouseguests"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/mouseguests/"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt; as MouseGuests (please follow!). And Raymie has become a travel agent specializing in Disney Vacations, so if you need help planning your next Disney vacation, go &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/smvbyraymie"&gt;follow her on Facebook&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="mailto:raymie@simplymagicalvacations.com"&gt;send her an email&lt;/a&gt;. We love talking about Disney World and Disneyland and these are our outlets for enjoying Disney while we’re away from the parks.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;To wrap up this introduction post, we thought we’d help you get to know us better by sharing some of our favorite things about Disney Parks.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="ulist"&gt; 
 &lt;ul&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Craig’s Favorites&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
   &lt;div class="ulist"&gt; 
    &lt;ul&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite park&lt;/strong&gt;: Disneyland, mostly because of the rich details and history and because it’s the only park that Walt actually walked in.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite attraction&lt;/strong&gt;: Even though I’m a thrill ride junkie, I can’t get enough of the Haunted Mansion and enjoy the details and subtle humor. After that, I’m a big fan of Pirates of the Caribbean, the Jungle Cruise, Big Thunder Mountain, Tower of Terror, and Radiator Springs Racers.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite show&lt;/strong&gt;: Paint the Night is amazing and my current favorite. That said, I thought that the original World of Color (not the current version, which I’m not much of a fan of) was the most incredible thing I’ve ever seen.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite resort hotel&lt;/strong&gt;: Port Orleans Riverside, because it’s where we stayed on our honeymoon and because it’s easily one of the nicest moderate resorts on Disney property. And the fact that Yehaa Bob performs there cinches it for me.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite restaurant&lt;/strong&gt;: It’s a toss-up. I love the burgers at Beaches and Cream (Beach Club), the kjøttkaker at Akershus (Epcot), the never-ending skillet of meat at Whispering Canyon (Wilderness Lodge) and the Monte Cristo at Cafe Orleans (Disneyland). It’s hard to decide between these. Honorable mention goes Be Our Guest (Magic Kingdom) and Liberty Tree Tavern (Magic Kingdom).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite snack&lt;/strong&gt;: Dole Whip. 'nuff said.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite character&lt;/strong&gt;: I share a birthday with Donald Duck (June 9), so there’s obviously a connection there. But when meeting the characters, it’s hard to beat the interaction with Gaston and the Tremaine family.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite movie&lt;/strong&gt;: The Jungle Book. It has great music, a good story, and it was the first Disney movie I ever saw in the theater (at a drive-in, no less).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
    &lt;/ul&gt; 
   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Raymie’s Favorites&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
   &lt;div class="ulist"&gt; 
    &lt;ul&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite park&lt;/strong&gt;: Disneyland Park, because of Fantasyland Theatre and ToonTown. She says it has more character and is really unique.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite attraction&lt;/strong&gt;: Soarin' because the smells and sights and movement immerses you in flight.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite show&lt;/strong&gt;: Fantasmic! Mickey’s up on the mountain and then suddenly he’s on the ground! It’s really well done; it’s amazing. Some imagination, huh!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite resort hotel&lt;/strong&gt;: Beach Club&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite restaurant&lt;/strong&gt;: Cafe Orleans because of the pommes frites!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite snack&lt;/strong&gt;: The gingerbread cupcake they had at Studio Catering Co. during Christmas.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite character&lt;/strong&gt;: Mickey Mouse. Hello, the guy’s hilarious!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite movie&lt;/strong&gt;: Little Mermaid&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
    &lt;/ul&gt; 
   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maisy’s Favorites&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
   &lt;div class="ulist"&gt; 
    &lt;ul&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite park&lt;/strong&gt;: Disneyland Park. Or, as she refers to it "Magic Kingdom in Disneyland" because she understands that this is Walt Disney’s original Magic Kingdom. (We’ve raised her right.)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite attraction&lt;/strong&gt;: Seven Dwarfs Mine Train in the Magic Kingdom&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite show&lt;/strong&gt;: Disneyland’s Fantasmic! She didn’t offer a reason, but we all know it’s because of the Peter Pan scene, the superior dragon, and the Mark Twain Riverboat.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite resort hotel&lt;/strong&gt;: Beach Club&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite restaurant&lt;/strong&gt;: Be Our Guest in the Magic Kingdom. She enjoys the pasta there.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite snack&lt;/strong&gt;: Churro.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite character&lt;/strong&gt;: Cinderella&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite movie&lt;/strong&gt;: Cinderella&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
    &lt;/ul&gt; 
   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Madi’s Favorites&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
   &lt;div class="ulist"&gt; 
    &lt;ul&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite park&lt;/strong&gt;: Disney California Adventure because it has Cars Land. Also Magic Kingdom because it’s fun and has more to do than the other parks.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite attraction&lt;/strong&gt;: Seven Dwarfs Mine Train, Buzz Lightyear’s Space Ranger Spin/Astroblasters, Toy Story Midway Mania&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite show&lt;/strong&gt;: Festival of the Lion King because, unlike Fantasmic or World of Color, you won’t get wet and cold.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite resort hotel&lt;/strong&gt;: Art of Animation&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite restaurant&lt;/strong&gt;: Chef Mickey’s&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite snack&lt;/strong&gt;: Mickey Ice Cream Bar&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite character&lt;/strong&gt;: Pluto because he’s a dog and she loves dogs&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite movie&lt;/strong&gt;: Bolt and Lady and the Tramp (because they have dogs)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
    &lt;/ul&gt; 
   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;/ul&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;And now that you know a little bit about us, tell us something about you. Leave a comment here to introduce yourself and tell us what some of your favorite Disney things are! And be sure to follow MouseGuests on &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/MouseGuests"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/mouseguests"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;, and/or &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/mouseguests/"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>MouseGuests</category>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 02:07:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/05/A-few-introductions-are-in-order.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-02-28T02:07:02Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These parks are made for walking</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/05/These-parks-are-made-for-walking.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;I had big plans of posting a trip report from our December stay at Beach Club, but have since decided that such an article would be extremely long and could be summarized simply with "It was a lot of fun!". So instead of giving a play by play on everything we did and everything we ate, I thought it’d be more informative to share how much we walked.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Although busses, boats, and monorails are helpful to get you from your resort to the parks, it’s up to you and your two feet to get you around once you arrive at a park. You may not realize it, but you can log a &lt;strong&gt;lot&lt;/strong&gt; of miles visiting Disney World or Disneyland. I’ve heard various numbers regarding the average number of miles a person walks per day in Disney World, but certainly it will depend on the individual and what they do. In short, your mileage may vary.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;I don’t currently own a FitBit or other tracking device. Raymie got one for Christmas, but that was after our trip, so it was of no use at that time. But having recently discovered that the Health app on my iPhone can track the number of steps and miles walked in a day, I decided to keep tabs on how much I walked using that app. Here are the results, including a brief explanation of what we did to get those miles):&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="ulist"&gt; 
 &lt;ul&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dec 15th&lt;/strong&gt; - 9.01 miles : We arrived mid-day and after a quick lunch at Beaches and Cream, we went to the Magic Kingdom, including an evening at Mickey’s Very Merry Christmas Party.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; Dec 16th&lt;/strong&gt; - 11.32 miles : We went back to the Magic Kingdom for the full day.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; Dec 17th&lt;/strong&gt; - 8.97 miles : We spent the full day at Animal Kingdom and then went back to the resort after the park closed. We had planned to go see Yehaa Bob, but everyone was tired and just wanted to go back and rest. While everyone else rested, I walked over to Epcot (from Beach Club) to see and photograph Illuminations. This added a few steps, but I found a place to watch along the bridge between UK and France, so it didn’t dramatically impact my miles.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; Dec 18th&lt;/strong&gt; - 9.15 miles : We spent the full day in Hollywood Studios. We had planned to see the Osborne Lights after the first Fantasmic! show, but didn’t realize that they shut them down early for Symphony in the Stars. This being the first night for Symphony in the Stars, the park was crazy busy, so we ended up just going back to the resort.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; Dec 19th&lt;/strong&gt; - 12.4 miles : We started our day in Epcot, spending most of the morning and early afternoon in Future World, before making brief circle around World Showcase. Then we caught a boat over to Hollywood Studios to see the Osborne Lights. My family went back to the resort to rest while I stayed back around the center stage area to see the Symphony in the Stars fireworks.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; Dec 20th&lt;/strong&gt; - 10.72 miles : We spent a full day in the Magic Kingdom, heading back only a little early to pack so we could leave the next day.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; Dec 21st&lt;/strong&gt; - 6.62 miles : Our last day was spent in the Magic Kingdom. The pre-Christmas crowds were really out in force, so we were limited on how much we could get done. After a few hours, we called it done and went back to the resort and from there to the airport to head home.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;/ul&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;In total, I walked 68.19 miles during that week-long trip, averaging 9.74 miles per day.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Of course, I can’t speak with any certainty to the accuracy of the iPhone Health app, so the actual miles may be different. I was concerned that bumpy rides would register false miles, so I tested it on the bus ride from Beach Club to Magic Kingdom and was surprised to find that it didn’t register any additional steps while on the bus. Strangely, while standing perfectly still in line for Soarin', I noticed that it had registered a few dozen steps. So again, take these numbers with a grain of salt.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;I’m looking forward to seeing what numbers I get on our upcoming trips to Disney World and Disneyland. This time I’ll be sure to capture data from Raymie’s FitBit as well as from my iPhone for comparison. It’ll also be interesting to see if the average miles per day in Disneyland will be any different from Disney World.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;One final thought: Because of all of the walking you’ll do in Disney Parks, be sure to wear comfortable shoes. I won’t recommend any specific shoe, because the shoe I’ve found to be most comfortable is a sandal (which is usually the worst choice for going to Disney). For some it may be good old fashioned tennis shoes. Or, if you’ve seen the episode of &lt;em&gt;Modern Family&lt;/em&gt; where they go to Disneyland, it was Minnie slippers that suited Gloria’s feet. Just be sure to find whatever shoes work best for you and to break them in good before going to the parks.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;How many miles have you logged when visiting Disney World or Disneyland? Leave a comment and let us know!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 02:07:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/05/These-parks-are-made-for-walking.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-02-28T02:07:02Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Same-day reservations to be available for Skipper Canteen</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/10/Same-day-reservations-to-be-available-for-Skipper-Canteen.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/SkipperCanteen600.jpg" alt="SkipperCanteen600.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The Jungle Navigation Company’s Skipper Canteen opened in late December, blending a unique dining experience with the fun (and corny jokes) of the Jungle Cruise. Unlike other table service restaurants in Disney World, however, Skipper Canteen has not been taking reservations and instead taking walk up guests as patrons. That changes tomorrow…​&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Starting tomorrow and scheduled to last until February 27th, guests wishing to enjoy the adventurous cuisine of the Skipper Canteen can make same-day reservations by visiting &lt;a href="http://jungleskippercanteen.com" class="bare"&gt;http://jungleskippercanteen.com&lt;/a&gt; or by calling 407-993-1933.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Although the Skipper Canteen was open on our last trip to Disney World, we had already planned our meals and couldn’t fit it into the trip. I’m hoping to give it a try on a future trip, however, with the "Skip’s Mac &amp;amp; Cheese" and "Tastes like Chicken…​because it is" being the two menu items that have caught my attention.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Have you dined at Skipper Canteen? What did you think? Leave a comment and let us know!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>News</category>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 02:07:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/10/Same-day-reservations-to-be-available-for-Skipper-Canteen.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-02-28T02:07:02Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Friday Favorites! What is your favorite Disney pizza place?</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/12/Friday-Favorites-What-is-your-favorite-Disney-pizza-place.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/FF_Pizza_orig.png" alt="FF Pizza orig.png"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;This past Tuesday was National Pizza Day, which has us wondering: What is your favorite place in Walt Disney World or Disneyland to get a slice or two of pizza?&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Do you like the flatbreads served at Pinocchio’s Village Haus? Maybe the wood-fired taste of Via Napoli in Epcot? How about a slice from Boardwalk Pizza &amp;amp; Pasta in Disney California Adventure? Or perhaps it’s the out of this world pizza at Redd Rocket’s Pizza Port in Disneyland. Do your adventures lead you to Pizzafari in Disney’s Animal Kingdom? Even though it’s future is uncertain, did you enjoy Pizza Planet in Disney’s Hollywood Studio?&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Even if it’s the PB&amp;amp;J pizza at Goofy’s Kitchen in the Disneyland Hotel, we want to hear from you! Where in Walt Disney World or Disneyland is your favorite place to get pizza? Leave a comment and let us know! And don’t forget to tell your friends, family, neighbors, classmates, fantasy football league, softball team, and pizza delivery person about MouseGuests and invite them to come join in on the conversation!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Friday Favorites</category>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 02:07:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/12/Friday-Favorites-What-is-your-favorite-Disney-pizza-place.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-02-28T02:07:02Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Friday Favorites! What is your favorite Disney queue?</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/19/Friday-Favorites-What-is-your-favorite-Disney-queue.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/FF_Queues.png" alt="FF Queues.png"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Although it’s the shows and attractions (and the food) at Disney Parks that gets all of the attention, let’s face it: We spend an enormous amount of time waiting to get to those headliners. Thankfully, many of the queues for Disney attractions are more than just switchbacks of ropes and chains. Some of them have interactive elements and others have fun things to look at while you wait.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;So this week, we want you to let us know which of the attraction queues is your favorite. Is it the fortress and armory in the Magic Kingdom’s Pirates of the Caribbean queue? How about the space exploration theme of Mission: SPACE in Epcot? Do you push books, play a haunted organ, and read the tombstones while waiting to enter the Magic Kingdom’s Haunted Mansion? Do the artifacts on display in the queue for Expedition Everest in Disneys Animal Kingdom build up the excitement for coming face to face with the Yeti? Do you enjoy seeing pictures and stories of the pioneers of air travel in the queue for Soarin' in Disney California Adventure? Or do your kids (or you…​admit it) like to dig around in Rabbit’s garden and smudge honey on the wall while waiting to ride The Many Adventures of Winnie the Pooh in the Magic Kingdom?&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Or maybe your favorite queue is the one with the shortest line?&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Leave a comment and let us know which attraction queue in Disney World or Disneyland is your favorite! And don’t wait there by yourself. Invite friends, family, everyone you see at the local farmer’s market, and everyone you can remember from high school to come follow MouseGuests and join in on the conversation!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;And be sure to follow us on &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/MouseGuests"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/mouseguests"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/mouseguests/"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt; for more Disney Parks fun and news!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Friday Favorites</category>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 02:07:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/19/Friday-Favorites-What-is-your-favorite-Disney-queue.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-02-28T02:07:02Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set your DVRs! Disneyland 60th Anniversary special on ABC</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/19/Set-your-DVRs-Disneyland-60th-Anniversary-special-on-ABC.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/wwod_d60.jpg" alt="wwod d60.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The ABC special &lt;em&gt;Wonderful World of Disney: Disneyland 60&lt;/em&gt; airs &lt;em&gt;this&lt;/em&gt; Sunday night. Celebrating Disneyland’s 60th Anniversary, this show will feature guest celebrities such as Harrison Ford, Idina Menzel, Tori Kelly, Kermit the Frog, Elton John, Pentatonix, Josh Gad, and many more, with Derek Hough serving as master of ceremonies. And, of course, we’ll get to see Disneyland itself as well as Disney California Adventure, including peeks at the &lt;em&gt;Paint the Night&lt;/em&gt; parade and &lt;em&gt;World of Color: Celebrate!&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;You will not want to miss this show! Clear your calendar, set your DVR (so you can watch it over and over again), and pop some corn (or make some homemade churros)…​and tune in to ABC at 8pm (7pm central) to celebrate Disneyland’s 60th Anniversary from the comfort of your home!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Who’s going to tune it? Leave a comment here and let us know what you’re most excited about when watching &lt;em&gt;Wonderful World of Disney: Disneyland 60&lt;/em&gt;. And then come back after the show and discuss it some more!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disneyland</category>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 02:07:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/19/Set-your-DVRs-Disneyland-60th-Anniversary-special-on-ABC.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-02-28T02:07:02Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star Wars Stage Show and New Fireworks coming to Hollywood Studios</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/19/Star-Wars-Stage-Show-and-New-Fireworks-coming-to-Hollywood-Studios.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/NewSWFireworks.jpeg" alt="NewSWFireworks.jpeg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;There’s been an awakening. Have you felt it?&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Disney’s Hollywood Studios is about to awaken with all new Star Wars experiences! The &lt;a href="https://disneyparks.disney.go.com/blog/2016/02/new-star-wars-nighttime-spectacular-announced-set-to-make-theme-park-history/"&gt;Disney Parks Blog&lt;/a&gt; is reporting that starting April 4th, a new Star Wars stage show named "&lt;em&gt;Star Wars: A Galaxy Far, Far Away&lt;/em&gt;" will debut at center stage in Disney’s Hollywood Studios. That same day, Captain Phasma (from &lt;em&gt;The Force Awakens&lt;/em&gt;) will lead several First Order stormtroopers on a march from the Star Wars Launch Bay to center stage.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;To top that off, later this summer, a new Star Wars fireworks show, "&lt;em&gt;Star Wars: A Galactic Spectacular&lt;/em&gt;" will be shown nightly, combining fireworks, special effects, and video projection on the Chinese Theater. The show will include a tower of fire and spotlight beams that form lightsabers in the sky.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Having seen the amazing Star Wars-themed "&lt;em&gt;Symphony in the Stars&lt;/em&gt;", both at Star Wars Weekends and the newer incarnation of the show that debuted in December, I can only imagine that the new show will be nothing short of jaw-dropping. And having seen the Star Wars segment of &lt;em&gt;World of Color&lt;/em&gt; in Disney California Adventure, I imagine the tower of fire being much like the huge fireballs shot during that show. This should be amazing!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;What do you think of all of the Star Wars experiences that Disney is offering in Disney’s Hollywood Studios in advance of the new Star Wars Land to be opened in a few years? Leave a comment and let’s discuss!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 02:07:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/19/Star-Wars-Stage-Show-and-New-Fireworks-coming-to-Hollywood-Studios.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-02-28T02:07:02Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toy Story Midway Mania closing March 15; Third track opening this summer</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/20/Toy-Story-Midway-Mania-closing-March-15-Third-track-opening-this-summer.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/PotatoHead.jpg" alt="PotatoHead.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;We’re hearing that &lt;em&gt;Toy Story Midway Mania&lt;/em&gt; in Disney’s Hollywood Studios is closing on March 15th for a one day refurb, likely to complete work in the queue area for a third track to be open sometime this summer.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Toy Story Midway Mania&lt;/em&gt; is one of the most popular attractions in not only Disney’s Hollywood Studios, but in all of Walt Disney World. This blend of dark ride and video game put guest in front of 3D screens where they shoot balls, throw darts at balloons, and toss pies to earn points.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The standby line for the attraction is almost always well over an hour and a half, in spite of the fact that it currently has two virtually identical tracks. The popularity of the attraction has prompted Disney to build a third track adjacent to the existing ride for additional capacity. With the third track construction nearing completion, one of the last steps in the project is to rework the queue to accommodate the new track. A similar project is underway in Epcot to add a third theater to the popular &lt;em&gt;Soarin'&lt;/em&gt; attraction, which is currently closed and expected to open sometime this summer.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;What do you think about this news? Do you welcome the new third track in hopes that it will make it possible for you to ride it more often without spending so much time in line? Leave a comment below and let us know.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;EDIT: Updated article to reflect that this is a one-day closure.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 02:07:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/20/Toy-Story-Midway-Mania-closing-March-15-Third-track-opening-this-summer.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-02-28T02:07:02Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our thoughts on Wonderful World of Disney: Disneyland 60</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/22/Our-thoughts-on-Wonderful-World-of-Disney-Disneyland-60.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/wwod_d60.jpg" alt="wwod d60.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Did you tune in to ABC last night to see &lt;em&gt;Wonderful World of Disney: Disneyland 60&lt;/em&gt;? We sure did and it was, in a word, fantastic! I won’t go over the whole show in detail, but instead will discuss a few hightlights and observations.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The show started out with Fallout Boy performing "I Wanna Be Like You" from Disney’s &lt;em&gt;The Jungle Book&lt;/em&gt;. I can’t say that I’m a big fan of Fall Out Boy, but I am a fan of the song so I was skeptical that they’d pull it off to my satisfaction. They exceeded my expectations and did a brilliant job covering the song.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Sir Elton John’s performance of "Circle of Life" was as great as you’d expect. I was not, however, excited about the new song "Wonderful Crazy Night". That’s not to say it was a bad song. Just nothing amazing, aside from the fireworks that were the backdrop for the song.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Josh Gad’s brief tour of Disneyland was a ton of fun. His energy, and of course his voice, made it feel as if you were watching Olaf (from &lt;em&gt;Frozen&lt;/em&gt;) give a tour of Disneyland.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Speaking of &lt;em&gt;Frozen&lt;/em&gt;, Idina Menzel’s performance of "Let it Go" in front of the water fountains in Disney California Adventure was good, but didn’t seem to carry the same emotion as the original recording.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The most amazing highlight of the show, in our opinion, was when Dick Van Dyke took the stage at the end of the "Step in Time" dance performance to channel his Bert character from &lt;em&gt;Mary Poppins&lt;/em&gt;. For a 90 year old man, he still has some amazing moves.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;A lot of people probably tuned in to hear more about the new &lt;em&gt;Star Wars&lt;/em&gt; lands coming to &lt;em&gt;Disneyland&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Disney’s Hollywood Studios&lt;/em&gt;. Harrison Ford introduced this section which was full of new concept art, including a better idea of what the Millenium Falcon attraction will look like. There was also what appeared to be a dark ride, perhaps an interactive dark ride (like &lt;em&gt;Buzz Lightyear’s Space Ranger Spin&lt;/em&gt;) that puts you in the middle of a battle with stormtroopers. They also mentioned an upscale dining experience as part of the new land. It all looks amazing, but it will take me a few days to fully digest and analyze what I saw.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The two other highlights were the performance of music from Star Wars and Fantasia. Of course, the music was fantastic, the backdrops and video shown during these performances made it more than just a listening experience.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;All in all, &lt;em&gt;Wonderful World of Disney&lt;/em&gt; was a fun review of Disney’s movies, music, and of Disneyland itself. That said, there was very little Disneyland in a show that purports to be a celebrate of Disneyland’s 60th anniversary. Most of the show took place outside of Disneyland. I was hoping to see more of the &lt;em&gt;Paint the Night Parade&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Disneyland Forever&lt;/em&gt;, not to mention several of the iconic Disneyland attractions. At best, only about 25% of the show was devoted to Disneyland.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Nevertheless, it was well worth watching and if you’ve DVR’d it, then you will probably watch it over and over again. I know we will. If, however, you want to see more of Disneyland and Disney California Adventure, then I recommend that you visit the parks, as the show is a let-down in that regard. (Email &lt;a href="mailto:raymie@simplymagicalvacations.com"&gt;raymie@simplymagicalvacations.com&lt;/a&gt; for free help in planning your trip to Disneyland or Disney World.)&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;What did you think of &lt;em&gt;Wonderful World of Disney: Disneyland 60&lt;/em&gt;? Leave a comment below and let us know.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disneyland</category>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 02:07:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/22/Our-thoughts-on-Wonderful-World-of-Disney-Disneyland-60.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-02-28T02:07:02Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mickey's Soundsational Parade live streaming event tomorrow</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/23/Mickeys-Soundsational-Parade-live-streaming-event-tomorrow.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/Soundsational_Bert.jpg" alt="Soundsational Bert.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;There’s no question that Disney puts on some amazing parades. One of the best parades that is currently run in the parks is &lt;em&gt;Mickey’s Soundsational Parade&lt;/em&gt; in Disneyland. Tomorrow when &lt;em&gt;Mickey’s Soundsational Parade&lt;/em&gt; steps off at 4:15pm Pacific (7:15pm Eastern), the &lt;a href="http://disneyparks.disney.go.com/blog"&gt;Disney Parks Blog&lt;/a&gt; will be streaming it live for you to watch from home!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;While not as much of a classic as the &lt;em&gt;Main Street Electrical Parade&lt;/em&gt; or as flashy as &lt;em&gt;Paint the Night&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Mickey’s Soundsational Parade&lt;/em&gt; is an incredibly fun parade with some great floats and an energetic soundtrack. And I’ll even be so bold as to suggest that the float designs are almost on par with those from &lt;em&gt;Disney’s Festival of Fantasy Parade&lt;/em&gt; in the Magic Kingdom.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The parade is led by Mickey Mouse playing drums while riding on a Mickey-shaped float. In fact, drums are a key component of every other float in the parade, with characters such as Aladdin, Donald Duck, Tinkerbell, and the &lt;em&gt;Lion King’s&lt;/em&gt; Simba riding atop drum-shaped floats. Other floats in the parade are themed more closely to the movies and characters they represent, including floats for &lt;em&gt;The Little Mermaid&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;The Princess and the Frog&lt;/em&gt;, and &lt;em&gt;Mary Poppins&lt;/em&gt;, as well as a float that carries Cinderella, Aurora, Belle, and Rapunzel.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Even though &lt;em&gt;Paint the Night&lt;/em&gt; has all of the attention for the past year, it’d be a mistake to visit Disneyland and miss &lt;em&gt;Mickey’s Soundsational Parade&lt;/em&gt;. Sadly, this was a mistake we made on our last trip to Disneyland, so we’re looking forward to making up for it in some small part by watching the live streaming event later today.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Visit the &lt;a href="http://disneyparks.disney.go.com/blog"&gt;Disney Parks Blog&lt;/a&gt; or keep an eye on this post to get details on where to watch the live stream event. We’ll update this post with a link as soon as we know more details. We also recommend, if possible, to hook your computer, smart phone, or tablet up to the biggest TV in your home for this event. We did that for the &lt;em&gt;Fantasmic!&lt;/em&gt; live streaming event last month and it made the experience so much more fun!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Are you looking forward to watching the &lt;em&gt;Mickey’s Soundsational Parade&lt;/em&gt; live streaming event? Leave a comment and let us know! And come back during or after the parade to share your thoughts on what you saw!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disneyland</category>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 02:07:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/23/Mickeys-Soundsational-Parade-live-streaming-event-tomorrow.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-02-28T02:07:02Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mickey's Soundsational Parade live stream tonight!</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/24/Mickeys-Soundsational-Parade-live-stream-tonight.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/Soundsational_Tink.jpg" alt="Soundsational Tink.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;We just wanted to remind you one more time about the live streaming event tonight presented by the &lt;a href="http://disneyparks.disney.go.com/blog"&gt;Disney Parks Blog&lt;/a&gt;. Starting at 4:30pm Pacific (7:20pm Eastern), they will be presenting &lt;em&gt;Mickey’s Soundsational Parade&lt;/em&gt;, live from Disneyland!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;For those who have never seen &lt;em&gt;Mickey’s Soundsational Parade&lt;/em&gt;, it is a highly energetic, musical celebration that starts in Fantasyland (near &lt;em&gt;it’s a small world&lt;/em&gt;) and moves down Main Street U.S.A., led by none other than Mickey Mouse playing drums on the lead float. It includes several beloved Disney characters including Peter Pan, Tinkerbell, Aurora, Cinderella, Belle, Rapunzel, Aladdin, the Genie, Tiana, Simba, and Mary Poppins. You won’t want to miss it!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Check back here closer to show time for any updates. And please leave a comment below letting us know what you think about &lt;em&gt;Mickey’s Soundsational Parade&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;UPDATE: Here’s the link to the YouTube stream (it should become live just before the streaming event starts): &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/embed/oLZwaVr-QEs" class="bare"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/embed/oLZwaVr-QEs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disneyland</category>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 02:07:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/24/Mickeys-Soundsational-Parade-live-stream-tonight.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-02-28T02:07:02Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luigi's Rollickin' Roadsters to open on March 7</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/25/Luigis-Rollickin-Roadsters-to-open-on-March-7.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/Luigis.jpg" alt="Luigis.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Disney is reporting that Luigi and Guido are returning from their trip to Italy and reopening Casa Della Tires in Disney California Adventure’s Cars Land. When it reopens on March 7th, so will &lt;em&gt;Luigi’s Rollickin' Roadsters&lt;/em&gt;, a trackless family ride where each car will have it’s own unique "dance" so that no two rides will be the same.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;When Cars Land opened in 2012, Casa Della Tires was the home to &lt;em&gt;Luigi’s Flying Tires&lt;/em&gt;, a ride where guests would ride tires on a cushion of air (think really big air hockey table). This was a throwback an early Disneyland attraction, &lt;em&gt;Flying Saucers&lt;/em&gt; in Tomorrowland. Unfortunately, the ride system relied heavily on guests actively leaning in different directions to move the tires and many (especially smaller children) had a difficult time moving the vehicles. So while Luigi and Guido went home to Italy, Disney Imagineers replaced it with &lt;em&gt;Luigi’s Rollickin' Roadsters&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;What do you think about this change? Will you miss &lt;em&gt;Luigi’s Flying Tires&lt;/em&gt;? Or are you looking forward to &lt;em&gt;Luigi’s Rollickin' Roadsters&lt;/em&gt;? Leave a comment and let us know!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disneyland</category>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 02:07:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/25/Luigis-Rollickin-Roadsters-to-open-on-March-7.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-02-28T02:07:02Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demand pricing expected at Disney World and Disneyland</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/26/Demand-pricing-expected-at-Disney-World-and-Disneyland.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/DL_TicketBooth.jpg" alt="DL TicketBooth.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;If you’re thinking about going to Disney World or Disneyland this year, you should consider getting your tickets &lt;em&gt;NOW&lt;/em&gt;. It’s been rumored for quite awhile and today we’ve heard from several sources that Disney will introduce demand pricing, based on expected crowd levels, very soon (possibly this weekend).&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The idea is that there are times of the year that the parks are busier than other times. During those times, with demand high, admission prices will be higher than on slower days. This is a good-news/bad-news proposition for guests. In theory, it may help even out the crowds, making some of the busier days less busy (while making some of the slower days busier). But it also means that if you want to visit Disney on a busy day, it may cost you more.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Demand pricing is not unusual in the travel industry. Airlines, hotels, and other resorts have employed it for years. Recently, Universal Studios Hollywood introduced demand pricing. And when Shanghai Disneyland opens this summer, it is expected to sell tickets with demand pricing.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The details of this new plan are still unknown. It’s unclear what effect, if any, it will have on tickets purchased as part of vacation packages. Stay tuned to this blog and we’ll update you as soon as we find out more. In the meantime, you may want to consider getting your tickets/vacation booked ASAP. May we suggest that you contact raymie@simplymagicalvacations (or click on the banner at the bottom of this page)?&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;What do you think of Disney’s plan to introduce demand pricing?&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 02:07:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/26/Demand-pricing-expected-at-Disney-World-and-Disneyland.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-02-28T02:07:02Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Friday Favorites! What is your favorite parade in Disney World or Disneyland?</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/26/Friday-Favorites-What-is-your-favorite-parade-in-Disney-World-or-Disneyland.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/FF_Parade.png" alt="FF Parade.png"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Earlier this week, we had a chance to watch &lt;em&gt;Mickey’s Soundsational Parade&lt;/em&gt;, live streamed from Disneyland. And this past Sunday night, we got a glimpse of Disneyland’s &lt;em&gt;Paint the Night Parade&lt;/em&gt; while watching &lt;em&gt;Wonderful World of Disney: Disneyland 60&lt;/em&gt; on ABC. No doubt, Disney knows how to put on a parade!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;So this week, we wanted to ask you which of Disney’s parades is your favorite? Does your foot tap along to the beat in &lt;em&gt;Mickey’s Soundsational Parade&lt;/em&gt;? Do you prefer the classic &lt;em&gt;Main Street Electrical Parade&lt;/em&gt;? Maybe it’s the wondrous and wonderful &lt;em&gt;Disney’s Festival of Fantasy Parade&lt;/em&gt; in the Magic Kingdom. How about the &lt;em&gt;Pixar Play Parade&lt;/em&gt; in Disney California Adventure? Or does &lt;em&gt;Paint the Night&lt;/em&gt; leaving you asking "When can we do this again?"?&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Since there are only a handful of parades currently running in Disney’s U.S. parks, feel free to suggest a retired parade or a parade from one of Disney’s parks in Paris, Tokyo, or Hong Kong. So if you loved &lt;em&gt;Spectromagic&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Tapestry of Nations&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Mickey’s Jammin' Jungle Parade&lt;/em&gt;, or Tokyo’s &lt;em&gt;Dreamlights&lt;/em&gt;, we want to hear from you!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Which Disney parade is your favorite? Leave a comment below and let us know. And don’t forget to tell your friends, neighbors, family, electrician, plumber, and everyone in the theater the next time you go see a movie, to come follow MouseGuests and join in on the fun!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Friday Favorites</category>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 02:07:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/26/Friday-Favorites-What-is-your-favorite-parade-in-Disney-World-or-Disneyland.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-02-28T02:07:02Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Table service dining coming to Diamond Horseshoe</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/26/Table-service-dining-coming-to-Diamond-Horseshoe.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/DiamondHorseshoe.jpg" alt="DiamondHorseshoe.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The Diamond Horseshoe in Disney World’s Magic Kingdom was an opening day dining location, as the east-coast equivalent of Disneyland’s Golden Horseshoe. But it has been only open rarely in the past dozen or so years. It has been used occasionally as overflow for Liberty Tree Tavern (which it shares a kitchen with) or as quick service, but many times we’ve walked by, it has been closed.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;That changes on March 13th!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Disney has announced that the Diamond Horseshoe will start serving both lunch and dinner as table service dining options. Guests dining at the Diamond Horseshoe will feast on an all-you-care-to-enjoy meal that starts with a Frontier Salad and cornbread, giving way to a choice of BBQ pulled turkey over cornbread, spit-roasted ham and country beans, or stewed beef with mashed potatoes. The dessert course will be a choice of an apple tart or a Campfire Brownie. The meal will be fixed price at $33 plus tax for adults or $19 for children ages 3-9.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;What do you think of this new addition to the Magic Kingdom’s dining lineup? Leave a comment and let us know!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 02:07:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/26/Table-service-dining-coming-to-Diamond-Horseshoe.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-02-28T02:07:02Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney announces price increase and seasonal pricing on 1-day tickets</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/27/Disney-announces-price-increase-and-seasonal-pricing-on-1-day-tickets.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/DL_TicketBooth.jpg" alt="DL TicketBooth.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;We reported yesterday that Disney is expected to introduce seasonal pricing (or demand pricing) this weekend. And now it is official. Starting tomorrow, 1-day tickets will be priced seasonally, based on demand. Disney presents this as a way to spread the crowds out, lowering the crowds on peak days by giving a pricing incentive to go on what are typically slower days.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The way it will work is that each month will have days that are designated as value, regular, and peak days. A 1-day ticket purchased for a value day will be less expensive than for a regular day which will be cheaper than for a peak day. It’s our understanding that 1-day Magic Kingdom ticket prices will be $124 for peak days, $110 for regular days, and $105 for value days, as compared to the current 1-day ticket price of $105. For the other parks in Disney World, the prices will be $114 (peak), $102 (regular), and $97 (value), as compared to the current 1-day ticket price of $97.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;As for Disneyland, the new price points for 1-day tickets will be $119 (peak), $105 (regular), and $95 (value), as compared to the current $99 price for 1-day tickets.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;We believe that seasonal pricing will have little effect on Walt Disney World guests, as those visiting Disney World typically purchase multi-day packages as part of a vacation package. Disneyland guests, on the other hand, are more likely to be impacted as many visitors to Disney’s west coast parks buy one day tickets, either because they’re locals or because they bunch their Disneyland trip in with other activities in the area.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;In addition, tickets prices are expected to go up tomorrow as well on both 1-day and multi-day ticket packages. We do not yet know the new price points, but stay tuned to this blog and we’ll update you as soon as we know more.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;If you’re planning a Disney World or Disneyland trip this year and have not yet purchased tickets or booked your vacation, we recommend you take care of that today before the prices go up. And in all cases, we advise that you always consider buying multi-day ticket packages as those will not be affected by seasonal pricing and the per-day price will be cheaper as you add more days. We recommend that you contact &lt;a href="mailto:raymie@simplymagicalvacations.com"&gt;raymie@simplymagicalvacations.com&lt;/a&gt; or by calling 214-236-7739 to get a free quote on your Disney vacation and snag those tickets before the prices go up.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;What do you think of seasonal pricing? Will this have an impact on a Disney trip you have in your future? Leave a comment and let us know!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 02:07:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/27/Disney-announces-price-increase-and-seasonal-pricing-on-1-day-tickets.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-02-28T02:07:02Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing Disney's new ticket prices</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/28/Analyzing-Disneys-new-ticket-prices.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/DL_TicketBooth.jpg" alt="DL TicketBooth.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Disney’s new ticket prices take effect today, including seasonal pricing for 1-day tickets. What does it mean and how will it impact your pocketbook when you buy tickets?&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;As we reported yesterday, the price for 1-day tickets will vary, depending on when you go, what park(s) you want to visit, and whether or not you buy the Park Hopper option. Suppose you want to go to the Magic Kingdom today. Today is considered a "Value" day, so the price of a 1-day ticket to the Magic Kingdom will be $105. If, however, you want to visit the Magic Kingdom next Sunday, which is a "Regular" day, the price goes up to $110. And most of the later portion of March is categorized as a "Peak" day, taking the price up to $124.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;On the other hand, should you want to visit Epcot, Hollywood Studios, or Animal Kingdom today, the price will be $97. Next Sunday it will be $102. And later in March it will go up to $114.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;If you want to be flexible and get the Park Hopper option, Value days will cost you $155, Regular days will be $160, and Peak days will ring up at $164, per 1-day ticket.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;But if you’re going to visit the parks for more than one day, then multi-day tickets are more economical and are not subject to seasonal pricing. And it gets cheaper per day as you add more days, with a 10-day ticket, without Park Hopper, being the cheapest per-day price point at $40 per day (before tax). The following table describes the prices for multi-day adult tickets (before tax):&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;table class="tableblock frame-all grid-all spread"&gt; 
 &lt;colgroup&gt; 
  &lt;col style="width: 33%;"&gt; 
  &lt;col style="width: 33%;"&gt; 
  &lt;col style="width: 33%;"&gt; 
 &lt;/colgroup&gt; 
 &lt;thead&gt; 
  &lt;tr&gt; 
   &lt;th class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;Days&lt;/th&gt; 
   &lt;th class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;w/o Park Hpper&lt;/th&gt; 
   &lt;th class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;w/Park Hopper&lt;/th&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt; 
 &lt;/thead&gt; 
 &lt;tbody&gt; 
  &lt;tr&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$202.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$257.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt; 
  &lt;tr&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;3&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$290.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$345.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt; 
  &lt;tr&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;4&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$325.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$395.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt; 
  &lt;tr&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;5&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$340.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$409.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt; 
  &lt;tr&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;6&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$355.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$424.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt; 
  &lt;tr&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;7&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$370.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$439.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt; 
  &lt;tr&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;8&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$380.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$449.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt; 
  &lt;tr&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;9&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$390.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$459.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt; 
  &lt;tr&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;10&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$400.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$469.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt; 
 &lt;/tbody&gt; 
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;To give you an idea of how this compares to multi-day prices before the price increase, we compared a multi-day ticket that we purchased before the price increase vs. what one would cost today. We paid $403.64 (incl. tax) for a 5-day ticket with Park Hopper a few weeks ago. Today that same ticket costs $435.59 (incl. tax) for a price difference of $31.95.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;What’s even more economical, it seems, is that if you buy multi-day tickets as part of a resort package (e.g., you stay at a Disney resort on property), the prices are even less expensive. A cursory review suggests that multi-day tickets with a resort package have not gone up at all.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;As for the effect on Disneyland prices, 1-day tickets will be priced at $95 for Value days, $105 for Regular days, and $119 for Peak days. Multi-day adult tickets are priced as follows (before tax):&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;table class="tableblock frame-all grid-all spread"&gt; 
 &lt;colgroup&gt; 
  &lt;col style="width: 33%;"&gt; 
  &lt;col style="width: 33%;"&gt; 
  &lt;col style="width: 33%;"&gt; 
 &lt;/colgroup&gt; 
 &lt;thead&gt; 
  &lt;tr&gt; 
   &lt;th class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;Days&lt;/th&gt; 
   &lt;th class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;w/o Park Hpper&lt;/th&gt; 
   &lt;th class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;w/Park Hopper&lt;/th&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt; 
 &lt;/thead&gt; 
 &lt;tbody&gt; 
  &lt;tr&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$195.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$235.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt; 
  &lt;tr&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;3&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$255.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$295.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt; 
  &lt;tr&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;4&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$280.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$320.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt; 
  &lt;tr&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;5&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$295.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$335.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt; 
 &lt;/tbody&gt; 
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;This makes the cheapest per-day price point for a Disneyland ticket $59 for a 5-day ticket without Park Hopper. (Disneyland doesn’t offer multi-day tickets for more than 5 days.)&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Disney is presenting this as a means of evening out crowd levels across the calender, giving a financial incentive to go during non-peak times. If it works, then the crazy holiday crowds seen around Christmas and Easter may be more tolerable, while non-peak days will become more crowded. If it doesn’t work, then guests buying 1-day tickets will be paying more to visit on days when the crowd levels will make it difficult to get their money’s worth; and those buying 1-day tickets for Value days will be paying less to have more room to move about.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;How do you feel about seasonal pricing? Do you think it will spread the crowds out more? Would you be willing to pay the Peak day prices for a single-day ticket? Or does it not matter to you because you’ll only ever buy multi-day tickets? Leave a comment below and let’s discuss it!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 16:13:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/28/Analyzing-Disneys-new-ticket-prices.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-02-28T16:13:43Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More magic coming to MyMagic+</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/01/More-magic-coming-to-MyMagic.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/MagicBands.jpg" alt="MagicBands.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Disney is expected to roll out two new features to MyMagic+ this Spring, including one that it seems &lt;em&gt;everyone&lt;/em&gt; has been asking for.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Currently, Walt Disney World guests are able to pre-select up to 3 attractions per day for FastPass+ (a benefit that lets you skip past the longer standby lines for many attractions). After having used those initial 3 FastPass+ selections, you can go to one of several kiosks in the parks and choose another FastPass+ option (and again until the day is over for additional FastPass+ choices). But in April guests will be able to use the My Disney Experience mobile app to make those additional selections right where they are at without having to wait in line at a kiosk.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The ability to select additional FastPass+ choices from the My Disney Experience app is a long overdue feature of the app. Many times the lines at the kiosks are longer than the standby lines for some of the attractions. And since you don’t even know what’s available until you get to a kiosk, you may have waited in line for nothing. We’ll certainly be making use of this on our next trip.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Additionally, Disney is expected to roll out StoryMaker, a feature of MyMagic+ that offers even greater interactivity in attractions and meet-n-greets. Using long-range RFID in MagicBands (the same way that on-ride photos are automatically linked to a guests My Disney Experience account now), a ride may know who a person is and where they are visiting from to "interact" with them. You may have noticed that some of the signs in the "Goodbye" room on &lt;em&gt;"it’s a small world"&lt;/em&gt; have been replaced with what appear to be TV monitors. Presumably, guests riding &lt;em&gt;"it’s a small world"&lt;/em&gt; will be greeted by name on those monitors as they pass through the "Goodbye" room. Similarly, meet-n-greet characters may greet a guest by name. Imagine walking up to Mickey Mouse and having him greet your personally by name!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;What do you think of these new MyMagic+ features? Leave a comment and let us know.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 19:07:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/01/More-magic-coming-to-MyMagic.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-03-01T19:07:58Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epcot International Flower and Garden Festival blooms today!</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/02/Epcot-International-Flower-and-Garden-Festival-blooms-today.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/MickeyTopiary.jpg" alt="MickeyTopiary.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;One of the most colorful times of the year blooms today at Epcot: The Epcot International Flower and Garden Festival!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Between now and May 30th, visitors to Epcot will experience a landscape that has come alive with colorful flowers and topiaries designed after beloved Disney and Pixar characters. If you have (or desire to have) a green thumb, there will also be gardening experts on-hand, giving tips on gardening at the festival center. And since gardening can build up an appetite, there are over a dozen outdoor kitchens setup around World Showcase, offering specialty dishes, desserts, and drinks.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;On the weekends, catch the rhythms and sounds of Garden Rocks Concert Series at the America Gardens Theater. This year, the concert series features:&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="ulist"&gt; 
 &lt;ul&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;March 4-6: The Orchestra starring former members of ELO&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;March 11-13: STARSHIP featuring Mickey Thomas&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;March 18-20: Little River Band&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;March 25-27: Village People&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;April 1-3: Herman’s Hermits starring Peter Noone&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;April 8-10: The Guess Who&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;April 15-17: Blood, Sweat, and Tears starring Bo Bice&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;April 22-24: Bad Company starring Brian Howe&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;April 29-May 1: Georgia Satellits&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;May 6-8: Gin Blossoms&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;May 13-15: Darlene Love&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;May 20-22: Night Ranger&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;May 27-30: The Spinners&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;/ul&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;That’s three months full of flowers, food, and music to take in when visiting Epcot!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Who’s going to be in Epcot during the Flower and Garden Festival this year? We’re going to be there one of those weekends, for sure. The last time we went we had lots of fun seeking out the topiaries. What are you looking forward to at this year’s festival? Leave a comment and let us know!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 14:36:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/02/Epcot-International-Flower-and-Garden-Festival-blooms-today.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-03-02T14:36:40Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"Finding Dory" characters joining Crush at Turtle Talk with Crush this summer</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/02/Finding-Dory-characters-joining-Crush-at-Turtle-Talk-with-Crush-this-summer.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/TurtleTalk.jpg" alt="TurtleTalk.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;New characts from Pixar’s "Finding Dory" will be swimming up to the "Human Tank" this summer at &lt;em&gt;Turtle Talk with Crush&lt;/em&gt; in both Epcot and Disney California Adventure. The new characters will include Destiny the whale shark, Bailey the beluga whale, and Hank the "septopus". Even the little dude, Squirt, will be joining his old man to answer questions from the humans.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;In case you’re unfamiliar with &lt;em&gt;Turtle Talk with Crush&lt;/em&gt;, it’s a wonderfully fun interactive show where Crush from "Finding Nemo" interacts with the audience (mostly the younger dudes, but sometimes their parentals) answering questions about marine life and asking a few questions he has about human life.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Have you ever been to &lt;em&gt;Turtle Talk with Crush&lt;/em&gt;? What do you think of adding these new characters to the show? Leave a comment and let us know.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 20:29:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/02/Finding-Dory-characters-joining-Crush-at-Turtle-Talk-with-Crush-this-summer.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-03-02T20:29:11Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rivers of Light to debut April 22 in Disney's Animal Kingdom</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/02/Rivers-of-Light-to-debut-April-22-in-Disneys-Animal-Kingdom.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/riversoflight.jpg" alt="riversoflight.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;After many months of anticipation, Disney has confirmed that the new &lt;em&gt;Rivers of Light&lt;/em&gt; nighttime spectacular will debut in Disney’s Animal Kingdom on April 22.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;This all new show, which takes place on the Discovery River between &lt;em&gt;Expedition Everest&lt;/em&gt; and the &lt;em&gt;Tree of Life&lt;/em&gt; will use water screen projections, lanterns, and projections on the &lt;em&gt;Tree of Life&lt;/em&gt; and surrounding landscape to tell a story of four animal Spirit Guides. Based on concept art and some sneak peaks offered by Disney Imagineers, this appears to be a nighttime spectacular on the same level as &lt;em&gt;World of Color&lt;/em&gt; in Disney California Adventure.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The April 22nd debut date is significant in that it is recognized as both Earth Day and as the 18th anniversary of Disney’s Animal Kingdom. And, we’re quite excited about &lt;em&gt;Rivers of Light&lt;/em&gt; debuting on this date, as it is a full week before we make our next visit to Disney World and so we will be able to see this new show shortly after it opens!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;What do you think about &lt;em&gt;Rivers of Light&lt;/em&gt; and the other nighttime activities coming to Disney’s Animal Kingdom in 2016? Leave a comment and let’s discuss!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 16:29:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/02/Rivers-of-Light-to-debut-April-22-in-Disneys-Animal-Kingdom.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-03-02T16:29:48Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Cruise Line to expand to six ships by 2023</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/03/Disney-Cruise-Line-to-expand-to-six-ships-by-2023.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/DCL202123.jpg" alt="DCL202123.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;In Disney’s annual shareholder’s meeting this morning (and then quickly followed by the disneyparks.disney.go.com/blog/[Disney Parks Blog]), Bob Iger confirmed that two new ships will be added to the Disney Cruise Line fleet. The first will come in 2021 and the next in 2023.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Our first thought was "What will they be named?" So far, no names have been revealed…​but we’ll keep you posted.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Have you ever taken a cruise on a Disney ship? If so, leave a comment and let us know what you thought about it. And let us know what you think of the expansion of Disney’s fleet!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney Cruise Line</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2016 15:47:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/03/Disney-Cruise-Line-to-expand-to-six-ships-by-2023.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-03-03T15:47:47Z</dc:date>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
