<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>MouseGuests!</title>
    <link>http://www.mouseguests.com</link>
    <description>Sharing our Disney obsession!</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 16:38:11 GMT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>mouseguests@habuma.com</dc:creator>
    <dc:date>2016-10-19T16:38:11Z</dc:date>
    <dc:language>en-US</dc:language>
    <item>
      <title>A few introductions are in order</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/05/A-few-introductions-are-in-order.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;After setting up this blog in December, we hopped on a plane and went to Disney World for a week. Then with the holidays and other activities consuming our time, we’re just now getting around to writing our first real blog post. As is customary, we’ll start by introducing ourselves and telling you a bit about how we became obsessed with Disney World and Disneyland.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;My name is Craig and I’ll probably be the one writing most of the articles here. Raymie is my beautiful and amazing wife and she is largely responsible for our Disney obsession. When we got married back in 1998, I asked her where she’d like to go on our honeymoon and she said Disney World. Neither of us had ever been before, so why not? I took care of the plans and booked us a week at Disney’s Dixie Landings Resort (now known as Port Orleans Riverside). It was an amazing trip! Even so, it’d be 10 years before we’d return…​&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Fast forward to 2008. By this time we had added Maisy and Madi, our two little princesses, to our family and decided to take them to Disney World. Maisy was 4 years old and Madi was 2. These ages were perfect for introducing them to Disney World and it was fun seeing it through their eyes. Of course, they were limited on what they could ride, so we spent a great deal of our time seeking out characters for photographs and autographs. Madi specifically wanted to meet Snow White so we went &lt;strong&gt;everywhere&lt;/strong&gt; to find her. Sadly we never found her. But it was a great trip nonetheless.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Three years passed before our next trip. By fall of 2011, Maisy had started figure skating and was invited to compete in a national figure skating competition in San Diego. While we were in California, we decided to drive up to Anaheim and visit Disneyland for our very first time. At that time construction walls were still up in California Adventure for Carthay Circle and Cars Land, but still had tons of fun. I recall finding Disneyland Park to have a lot of charm and character as compared to the Magic Kingdom, even if smaller.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;At this point our Disney obsession kicked into high gear with several trips in a row. I won’t bore you with mini trip reports for each trip, but here’s a summary of all of the Disney vacations we’ve taken thus far:&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="ulist"&gt; 
 &lt;ul&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dec 1998 : Walt Disney World (Dixie Landings)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dec 2008 : Walt Disney World (Caribbean Beach Resort)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;Aug 2011 : Disneyland (Good Neighbor Hotel)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dec 2012 : Walt Disney World (Port Orleans Riverside)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;Sep 2013 : Disneyland (Paradise Pier Hotel)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dec 2013 : Walt Disney World (Port Orleans Riverside)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;May 2014 : Walt Disney World (Port Orleans Riverside)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;Jan 2015 : Walt Disney World (Art of Animation)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;May 2015 : Disneyland (Grand Californian)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dec 2015 : Walt Disney World (Beach Club)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;/ul&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;We’re already planning for trips to Disney World this May and Disneyland in June. And we’ve even started talking about taking a Disney Cruise!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Suffice it to say, we’re obsessed. Along the way, I started posting to &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/MouseGuests"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/mouseguests"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/mouseguests/"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt; as MouseGuests (please follow!). And Raymie has become a travel agent specializing in Disney Vacations, so if you need help planning your next Disney vacation, go &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/smvbyraymie"&gt;follow her on Facebook&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="mailto:raymie@simplymagicalvacations.com"&gt;send her an email&lt;/a&gt;. We love talking about Disney World and Disneyland and these are our outlets for enjoying Disney while we’re away from the parks.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;To wrap up this introduction post, we thought we’d help you get to know us better by sharing some of our favorite things about Disney Parks.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="ulist"&gt; 
 &lt;ul&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Craig’s Favorites&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
   &lt;div class="ulist"&gt; 
    &lt;ul&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite park&lt;/strong&gt;: Disneyland, mostly because of the rich details and history and because it’s the only park that Walt actually walked in.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite attraction&lt;/strong&gt;: Even though I’m a thrill ride junkie, I can’t get enough of the Haunted Mansion and enjoy the details and subtle humor. After that, I’m a big fan of Pirates of the Caribbean, the Jungle Cruise, Big Thunder Mountain, Tower of Terror, and Radiator Springs Racers.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite show&lt;/strong&gt;: Paint the Night is amazing and my current favorite. That said, I thought that the original World of Color (not the current version, which I’m not much of a fan of) was the most incredible thing I’ve ever seen.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite resort hotel&lt;/strong&gt;: Port Orleans Riverside, because it’s where we stayed on our honeymoon and because it’s easily one of the nicest moderate resorts on Disney property. And the fact that Yehaa Bob performs there cinches it for me.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite restaurant&lt;/strong&gt;: It’s a toss-up. I love the burgers at Beaches and Cream (Beach Club), the kjøttkaker at Akershus (Epcot), the never-ending skillet of meat at Whispering Canyon (Wilderness Lodge) and the Monte Cristo at Cafe Orleans (Disneyland). It’s hard to decide between these. Honorable mention goes Be Our Guest (Magic Kingdom) and Liberty Tree Tavern (Magic Kingdom).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite snack&lt;/strong&gt;: Dole Whip. 'nuff said.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite character&lt;/strong&gt;: I share a birthday with Donald Duck (June 9), so there’s obviously a connection there. But when meeting the characters, it’s hard to beat the interaction with Gaston and the Tremaine family.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite movie&lt;/strong&gt;: The Jungle Book. It has great music, a good story, and it was the first Disney movie I ever saw in the theater (at a drive-in, no less).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
    &lt;/ul&gt; 
   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Raymie’s Favorites&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
   &lt;div class="ulist"&gt; 
    &lt;ul&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite park&lt;/strong&gt;: Disneyland Park, because of Fantasyland Theatre and ToonTown. She says it has more character and is really unique.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite attraction&lt;/strong&gt;: Soarin' because the smells and sights and movement immerses you in flight.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite show&lt;/strong&gt;: Fantasmic! Mickey’s up on the mountain and then suddenly he’s on the ground! It’s really well done; it’s amazing. Some imagination, huh!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite resort hotel&lt;/strong&gt;: Beach Club&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite restaurant&lt;/strong&gt;: Cafe Orleans because of the pommes frites!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite snack&lt;/strong&gt;: The gingerbread cupcake they had at Studio Catering Co. during Christmas.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite character&lt;/strong&gt;: Mickey Mouse. Hello, the guy’s hilarious!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite movie&lt;/strong&gt;: Little Mermaid&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
    &lt;/ul&gt; 
   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maisy’s Favorites&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
   &lt;div class="ulist"&gt; 
    &lt;ul&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite park&lt;/strong&gt;: Disneyland Park. Or, as she refers to it "Magic Kingdom in Disneyland" because she understands that this is Walt Disney’s original Magic Kingdom. (We’ve raised her right.)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite attraction&lt;/strong&gt;: Seven Dwarfs Mine Train in the Magic Kingdom&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite show&lt;/strong&gt;: Disneyland’s Fantasmic! She didn’t offer a reason, but we all know it’s because of the Peter Pan scene, the superior dragon, and the Mark Twain Riverboat.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite resort hotel&lt;/strong&gt;: Beach Club&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite restaurant&lt;/strong&gt;: Be Our Guest in the Magic Kingdom. She enjoys the pasta there.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite snack&lt;/strong&gt;: Churro.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite character&lt;/strong&gt;: Cinderella&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite movie&lt;/strong&gt;: Cinderella&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
    &lt;/ul&gt; 
   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Madi’s Favorites&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
   &lt;div class="ulist"&gt; 
    &lt;ul&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite park&lt;/strong&gt;: Disney California Adventure because it has Cars Land. Also Magic Kingdom because it’s fun and has more to do than the other parks.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite attraction&lt;/strong&gt;: Seven Dwarfs Mine Train, Buzz Lightyear’s Space Ranger Spin/Astroblasters, Toy Story Midway Mania&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite show&lt;/strong&gt;: Festival of the Lion King because, unlike Fantasmic or World of Color, you won’t get wet and cold.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite resort hotel&lt;/strong&gt;: Art of Animation&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite restaurant&lt;/strong&gt;: Chef Mickey’s&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite snack&lt;/strong&gt;: Mickey Ice Cream Bar&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite character&lt;/strong&gt;: Pluto because he’s a dog and she loves dogs&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
     &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Favorite movie&lt;/strong&gt;: Bolt and Lady and the Tramp (because they have dogs)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
    &lt;/ul&gt; 
   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;/ul&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;And now that you know a little bit about us, tell us something about you. Leave a comment here to introduce yourself and tell us what some of your favorite Disney things are! And be sure to follow MouseGuests on &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/MouseGuests"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/mouseguests"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;, and/or &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/mouseguests/"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>MouseGuests</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/05/A-few-introductions-are-in-order.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These parks are made for walking</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/05/These-parks-are-made-for-walking.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;I had big plans of posting a trip report from our December stay at Beach Club, but have since decided that such an article would be extremely long and could be summarized simply with "It was a lot of fun!". So instead of giving a play by play on everything we did and everything we ate, I thought it’d be more informative to share how much we walked.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Although busses, boats, and monorails are helpful to get you from your resort to the parks, it’s up to you and your two feet to get you around once you arrive at a park. You may not realize it, but you can log a &lt;strong&gt;lot&lt;/strong&gt; of miles visiting Disney World or Disneyland. I’ve heard various numbers regarding the average number of miles a person walks per day in Disney World, but certainly it will depend on the individual and what they do. In short, your mileage may vary.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;I don’t currently own a FitBit or other tracking device. Raymie got one for Christmas, but that was after our trip, so it was of no use at that time. But having recently discovered that the Health app on my iPhone can track the number of steps and miles walked in a day, I decided to keep tabs on how much I walked using that app. Here are the results, including a brief explanation of what we did to get those miles):&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="ulist"&gt; 
 &lt;ul&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dec 15th&lt;/strong&gt; - 9.01 miles : We arrived mid-day and after a quick lunch at Beaches and Cream, we went to the Magic Kingdom, including an evening at Mickey’s Very Merry Christmas Party.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; Dec 16th&lt;/strong&gt; - 11.32 miles : We went back to the Magic Kingdom for the full day.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; Dec 17th&lt;/strong&gt; - 8.97 miles : We spent the full day at Animal Kingdom and then went back to the resort after the park closed. We had planned to go see Yehaa Bob, but everyone was tired and just wanted to go back and rest. While everyone else rested, I walked over to Epcot (from Beach Club) to see and photograph Illuminations. This added a few steps, but I found a place to watch along the bridge between UK and France, so it didn’t dramatically impact my miles.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; Dec 18th&lt;/strong&gt; - 9.15 miles : We spent the full day in Hollywood Studios. We had planned to see the Osborne Lights after the first Fantasmic! show, but didn’t realize that they shut them down early for Symphony in the Stars. This being the first night for Symphony in the Stars, the park was crazy busy, so we ended up just going back to the resort.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; Dec 19th&lt;/strong&gt; - 12.4 miles : We started our day in Epcot, spending most of the morning and early afternoon in Future World, before making brief circle around World Showcase. Then we caught a boat over to Hollywood Studios to see the Osborne Lights. My family went back to the resort to rest while I stayed back around the center stage area to see the Symphony in the Stars fireworks.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; Dec 20th&lt;/strong&gt; - 10.72 miles : We spent a full day in the Magic Kingdom, heading back only a little early to pack so we could leave the next day.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; Dec 21st&lt;/strong&gt; - 6.62 miles : Our last day was spent in the Magic Kingdom. The pre-Christmas crowds were really out in force, so we were limited on how much we could get done. After a few hours, we called it done and went back to the resort and from there to the airport to head home.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;/ul&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;In total, I walked 68.19 miles during that week-long trip, averaging 9.74 miles per day.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Of course, I can’t speak with any certainty to the accuracy of the iPhone Health app, so the actual miles may be different. I was concerned that bumpy rides would register false miles, so I tested it on the bus ride from Beach Club to Magic Kingdom and was surprised to find that it didn’t register any additional steps while on the bus. Strangely, while standing perfectly still in line for Soarin', I noticed that it had registered a few dozen steps. So again, take these numbers with a grain of salt.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;I’m looking forward to seeing what numbers I get on our upcoming trips to Disney World and Disneyland. This time I’ll be sure to capture data from Raymie’s FitBit as well as from my iPhone for comparison. It’ll also be interesting to see if the average miles per day in Disneyland will be any different from Disney World.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;One final thought: Because of all of the walking you’ll do in Disney Parks, be sure to wear comfortable shoes. I won’t recommend any specific shoe, because the shoe I’ve found to be most comfortable is a sandal (which is usually the worst choice for going to Disney). For some it may be good old fashioned tennis shoes. Or, if you’ve seen the episode of &lt;em&gt;Modern Family&lt;/em&gt; where they go to Disneyland, it was Minnie slippers that suited Gloria’s feet. Just be sure to find whatever shoes work best for you and to break them in good before going to the parks.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;How many miles have you logged when visiting Disney World or Disneyland? Leave a comment and let us know!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/05/These-parks-are-made-for-walking.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Same-day reservations to be available for Skipper Canteen</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/10/Same-day-reservations-to-be-available-for-Skipper-Canteen.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/SkipperCanteen600.jpg" alt="SkipperCanteen600.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The Jungle Navigation Company’s Skipper Canteen opened in late December, blending a unique dining experience with the fun (and corny jokes) of the Jungle Cruise. Unlike other table service restaurants in Disney World, however, Skipper Canteen has not been taking reservations and instead taking walk up guests as patrons. That changes tomorrow…​&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Starting tomorrow and scheduled to last until February 27th, guests wishing to enjoy the adventurous cuisine of the Skipper Canteen can make same-day reservations by visiting &lt;a href="http://jungleskippercanteen.com" class="bare"&gt;http://jungleskippercanteen.com&lt;/a&gt; or by calling 407-993-1933.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Although the Skipper Canteen was open on our last trip to Disney World, we had already planned our meals and couldn’t fit it into the trip. I’m hoping to give it a try on a future trip, however, with the "Skip’s Mac &amp;amp; Cheese" and "Tastes like Chicken…​because it is" being the two menu items that have caught my attention.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Have you dined at Skipper Canteen? What did you think? Leave a comment and let us know!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>News</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/10/Same-day-reservations-to-be-available-for-Skipper-Canteen.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Friday Favorites! What is your favorite Disney pizza place?</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/12/Friday-Favorites-What-is-your-favorite-Disney-pizza-place.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/FF_Pizza_orig.png" alt="FF Pizza orig.png"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;This past Tuesday was National Pizza Day, which has us wondering: What is your favorite place in Walt Disney World or Disneyland to get a slice or two of pizza?&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Do you like the flatbreads served at Pinocchio’s Village Haus? Maybe the wood-fired taste of Via Napoli in Epcot? How about a slice from Boardwalk Pizza &amp;amp; Pasta in Disney California Adventure? Or perhaps it’s the out of this world pizza at Redd Rocket’s Pizza Port in Disneyland. Do your adventures lead you to Pizzafari in Disney’s Animal Kingdom? Even though it’s future is uncertain, did you enjoy Pizza Planet in Disney’s Hollywood Studio?&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Even if it’s the PB&amp;amp;J pizza at Goofy’s Kitchen in the Disneyland Hotel, we want to hear from you! Where in Walt Disney World or Disneyland is your favorite place to get pizza? Leave a comment and let us know! And don’t forget to tell your friends, family, neighbors, classmates, fantasy football league, softball team, and pizza delivery person about MouseGuests and invite them to come join in on the conversation!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Friday Favorites</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/12/Friday-Favorites-What-is-your-favorite-Disney-pizza-place.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Friday Favorites! What is your favorite Disney queue?</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/19/Friday-Favorites-What-is-your-favorite-Disney-queue.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/FF_Queues.png" alt="FF Queues.png"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Although it’s the shows and attractions (and the food) at Disney Parks that gets all of the attention, let’s face it: We spend an enormous amount of time waiting to get to those headliners. Thankfully, many of the queues for Disney attractions are more than just switchbacks of ropes and chains. Some of them have interactive elements and others have fun things to look at while you wait.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;So this week, we want you to let us know which of the attraction queues is your favorite. Is it the fortress and armory in the Magic Kingdom’s Pirates of the Caribbean queue? How about the space exploration theme of Mission: SPACE in Epcot? Do you push books, play a haunted organ, and read the tombstones while waiting to enter the Magic Kingdom’s Haunted Mansion? Do the artifacts on display in the queue for Expedition Everest in Disneys Animal Kingdom build up the excitement for coming face to face with the Yeti? Do you enjoy seeing pictures and stories of the pioneers of air travel in the queue for Soarin' in Disney California Adventure? Or do your kids (or you…​admit it) like to dig around in Rabbit’s garden and smudge honey on the wall while waiting to ride The Many Adventures of Winnie the Pooh in the Magic Kingdom?&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Or maybe your favorite queue is the one with the shortest line?&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Leave a comment and let us know which attraction queue in Disney World or Disneyland is your favorite! And don’t wait there by yourself. Invite friends, family, everyone you see at the local farmer’s market, and everyone you can remember from high school to come follow MouseGuests and join in on the conversation!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;And be sure to follow us on &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/MouseGuests"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/mouseguests"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/mouseguests/"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt; for more Disney Parks fun and news!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Friday Favorites</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/19/Friday-Favorites-What-is-your-favorite-Disney-queue.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set your DVRs! Disneyland 60th Anniversary special on ABC</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/19/Set-your-DVRs-Disneyland-60th-Anniversary-special-on-ABC.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/wwod_d60.jpg" alt="wwod d60.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The ABC special &lt;em&gt;Wonderful World of Disney: Disneyland 60&lt;/em&gt; airs &lt;em&gt;this&lt;/em&gt; Sunday night. Celebrating Disneyland’s 60th Anniversary, this show will feature guest celebrities such as Harrison Ford, Idina Menzel, Tori Kelly, Kermit the Frog, Elton John, Pentatonix, Josh Gad, and many more, with Derek Hough serving as master of ceremonies. And, of course, we’ll get to see Disneyland itself as well as Disney California Adventure, including peeks at the &lt;em&gt;Paint the Night&lt;/em&gt; parade and &lt;em&gt;World of Color: Celebrate!&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;You will not want to miss this show! Clear your calendar, set your DVR (so you can watch it over and over again), and pop some corn (or make some homemade churros)…​and tune in to ABC at 8pm (7pm central) to celebrate Disneyland’s 60th Anniversary from the comfort of your home!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Who’s going to tune it? Leave a comment here and let us know what you’re most excited about when watching &lt;em&gt;Wonderful World of Disney: Disneyland 60&lt;/em&gt;. And then come back after the show and discuss it some more!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disneyland</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/19/Set-your-DVRs-Disneyland-60th-Anniversary-special-on-ABC.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star Wars Stage Show and New Fireworks coming to Hollywood Studios</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/19/Star-Wars-Stage-Show-and-New-Fireworks-coming-to-Hollywood-Studios.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/NewSWFireworks.jpeg" alt="NewSWFireworks.jpeg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;There’s been an awakening. Have you felt it?&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Disney’s Hollywood Studios is about to awaken with all new Star Wars experiences! The &lt;a href="https://disneyparks.disney.go.com/blog/2016/02/new-star-wars-nighttime-spectacular-announced-set-to-make-theme-park-history/"&gt;Disney Parks Blog&lt;/a&gt; is reporting that starting April 4th, a new Star Wars stage show named "&lt;em&gt;Star Wars: A Galaxy Far, Far Away&lt;/em&gt;" will debut at center stage in Disney’s Hollywood Studios. That same day, Captain Phasma (from &lt;em&gt;The Force Awakens&lt;/em&gt;) will lead several First Order stormtroopers on a march from the Star Wars Launch Bay to center stage.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;To top that off, later this summer, a new Star Wars fireworks show, "&lt;em&gt;Star Wars: A Galactic Spectacular&lt;/em&gt;" will be shown nightly, combining fireworks, special effects, and video projection on the Chinese Theater. The show will include a tower of fire and spotlight beams that form lightsabers in the sky.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Having seen the amazing Star Wars-themed "&lt;em&gt;Symphony in the Stars&lt;/em&gt;", both at Star Wars Weekends and the newer incarnation of the show that debuted in December, I can only imagine that the new show will be nothing short of jaw-dropping. And having seen the Star Wars segment of &lt;em&gt;World of Color&lt;/em&gt; in Disney California Adventure, I imagine the tower of fire being much like the huge fireballs shot during that show. This should be amazing!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;What do you think of all of the Star Wars experiences that Disney is offering in Disney’s Hollywood Studios in advance of the new Star Wars Land to be opened in a few years? Leave a comment and let’s discuss!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/19/Star-Wars-Stage-Show-and-New-Fireworks-coming-to-Hollywood-Studios.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toy Story Midway Mania closing March 15; Third track opening this summer</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/20/Toy-Story-Midway-Mania-closing-March-15-Third-track-opening-this-summer.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/PotatoHead.jpg" alt="PotatoHead.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;We’re hearing that &lt;em&gt;Toy Story Midway Mania&lt;/em&gt; in Disney’s Hollywood Studios is closing on March 15th for a one day refurb, likely to complete work in the queue area for a third track to be open sometime this summer.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Toy Story Midway Mania&lt;/em&gt; is one of the most popular attractions in not only Disney’s Hollywood Studios, but in all of Walt Disney World. This blend of dark ride and video game put guest in front of 3D screens where they shoot balls, throw darts at balloons, and toss pies to earn points.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The standby line for the attraction is almost always well over an hour and a half, in spite of the fact that it currently has two virtually identical tracks. The popularity of the attraction has prompted Disney to build a third track adjacent to the existing ride for additional capacity. With the third track construction nearing completion, one of the last steps in the project is to rework the queue to accommodate the new track. A similar project is underway in Epcot to add a third theater to the popular &lt;em&gt;Soarin'&lt;/em&gt; attraction, which is currently closed and expected to open sometime this summer.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;What do you think about this news? Do you welcome the new third track in hopes that it will make it possible for you to ride it more often without spending so much time in line? Leave a comment below and let us know.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;EDIT: Updated article to reflect that this is a one-day closure.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/20/Toy-Story-Midway-Mania-closing-March-15-Third-track-opening-this-summer.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our thoughts on Wonderful World of Disney: Disneyland 60</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/22/Our-thoughts-on-Wonderful-World-of-Disney-Disneyland-60.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/wwod_d60.jpg" alt="wwod d60.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Did you tune in to ABC last night to see &lt;em&gt;Wonderful World of Disney: Disneyland 60&lt;/em&gt;? We sure did and it was, in a word, fantastic! I won’t go over the whole show in detail, but instead will discuss a few hightlights and observations.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The show started out with Fallout Boy performing "I Wanna Be Like You" from Disney’s &lt;em&gt;The Jungle Book&lt;/em&gt;. I can’t say that I’m a big fan of Fall Out Boy, but I am a fan of the song so I was skeptical that they’d pull it off to my satisfaction. They exceeded my expectations and did a brilliant job covering the song.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Sir Elton John’s performance of "Circle of Life" was as great as you’d expect. I was not, however, excited about the new song "Wonderful Crazy Night". That’s not to say it was a bad song. Just nothing amazing, aside from the fireworks that were the backdrop for the song.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Josh Gad’s brief tour of Disneyland was a ton of fun. His energy, and of course his voice, made it feel as if you were watching Olaf (from &lt;em&gt;Frozen&lt;/em&gt;) give a tour of Disneyland.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Speaking of &lt;em&gt;Frozen&lt;/em&gt;, Idina Menzel’s performance of "Let it Go" in front of the water fountains in Disney California Adventure was good, but didn’t seem to carry the same emotion as the original recording.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The most amazing highlight of the show, in our opinion, was when Dick Van Dyke took the stage at the end of the "Step in Time" dance performance to channel his Bert character from &lt;em&gt;Mary Poppins&lt;/em&gt;. For a 90 year old man, he still has some amazing moves.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;A lot of people probably tuned in to hear more about the new &lt;em&gt;Star Wars&lt;/em&gt; lands coming to &lt;em&gt;Disneyland&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Disney’s Hollywood Studios&lt;/em&gt;. Harrison Ford introduced this section which was full of new concept art, including a better idea of what the Millenium Falcon attraction will look like. There was also what appeared to be a dark ride, perhaps an interactive dark ride (like &lt;em&gt;Buzz Lightyear’s Space Ranger Spin&lt;/em&gt;) that puts you in the middle of a battle with stormtroopers. They also mentioned an upscale dining experience as part of the new land. It all looks amazing, but it will take me a few days to fully digest and analyze what I saw.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The two other highlights were the performance of music from Star Wars and Fantasia. Of course, the music was fantastic, the backdrops and video shown during these performances made it more than just a listening experience.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;All in all, &lt;em&gt;Wonderful World of Disney&lt;/em&gt; was a fun review of Disney’s movies, music, and of Disneyland itself. That said, there was very little Disneyland in a show that purports to be a celebrate of Disneyland’s 60th anniversary. Most of the show took place outside of Disneyland. I was hoping to see more of the &lt;em&gt;Paint the Night Parade&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Disneyland Forever&lt;/em&gt;, not to mention several of the iconic Disneyland attractions. At best, only about 25% of the show was devoted to Disneyland.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Nevertheless, it was well worth watching and if you’ve DVR’d it, then you will probably watch it over and over again. I know we will. If, however, you want to see more of Disneyland and Disney California Adventure, then I recommend that you visit the parks, as the show is a let-down in that regard. (Email &lt;a href="mailto:raymie@simplymagicalvacations.com"&gt;raymie@simplymagicalvacations.com&lt;/a&gt; for free help in planning your trip to Disneyland or Disney World.)&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;What did you think of &lt;em&gt;Wonderful World of Disney: Disneyland 60&lt;/em&gt;? Leave a comment below and let us know.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disneyland</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/22/Our-thoughts-on-Wonderful-World-of-Disney-Disneyland-60.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mickey's Soundsational Parade live streaming event tomorrow</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/23/Mickeys-Soundsational-Parade-live-streaming-event-tomorrow.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/Soundsational_Bert.jpg" alt="Soundsational Bert.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;There’s no question that Disney puts on some amazing parades. One of the best parades that is currently run in the parks is &lt;em&gt;Mickey’s Soundsational Parade&lt;/em&gt; in Disneyland. Tomorrow when &lt;em&gt;Mickey’s Soundsational Parade&lt;/em&gt; steps off at 4:15pm Pacific (7:15pm Eastern), the &lt;a href="http://disneyparks.disney.go.com/blog"&gt;Disney Parks Blog&lt;/a&gt; will be streaming it live for you to watch from home!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;While not as much of a classic as the &lt;em&gt;Main Street Electrical Parade&lt;/em&gt; or as flashy as &lt;em&gt;Paint the Night&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Mickey’s Soundsational Parade&lt;/em&gt; is an incredibly fun parade with some great floats and an energetic soundtrack. And I’ll even be so bold as to suggest that the float designs are almost on par with those from &lt;em&gt;Disney’s Festival of Fantasy Parade&lt;/em&gt; in the Magic Kingdom.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The parade is led by Mickey Mouse playing drums while riding on a Mickey-shaped float. In fact, drums are a key component of every other float in the parade, with characters such as Aladdin, Donald Duck, Tinkerbell, and the &lt;em&gt;Lion King’s&lt;/em&gt; Simba riding atop drum-shaped floats. Other floats in the parade are themed more closely to the movies and characters they represent, including floats for &lt;em&gt;The Little Mermaid&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;The Princess and the Frog&lt;/em&gt;, and &lt;em&gt;Mary Poppins&lt;/em&gt;, as well as a float that carries Cinderella, Aurora, Belle, and Rapunzel.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Even though &lt;em&gt;Paint the Night&lt;/em&gt; has all of the attention for the past year, it’d be a mistake to visit Disneyland and miss &lt;em&gt;Mickey’s Soundsational Parade&lt;/em&gt;. Sadly, this was a mistake we made on our last trip to Disneyland, so we’re looking forward to making up for it in some small part by watching the live streaming event later today.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Visit the &lt;a href="http://disneyparks.disney.go.com/blog"&gt;Disney Parks Blog&lt;/a&gt; or keep an eye on this post to get details on where to watch the live stream event. We’ll update this post with a link as soon as we know more details. We also recommend, if possible, to hook your computer, smart phone, or tablet up to the biggest TV in your home for this event. We did that for the &lt;em&gt;Fantasmic!&lt;/em&gt; live streaming event last month and it made the experience so much more fun!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Are you looking forward to watching the &lt;em&gt;Mickey’s Soundsational Parade&lt;/em&gt; live streaming event? Leave a comment and let us know! And come back during or after the parade to share your thoughts on what you saw!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disneyland</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/23/Mickeys-Soundsational-Parade-live-streaming-event-tomorrow.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mickey's Soundsational Parade live stream tonight!</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/24/Mickeys-Soundsational-Parade-live-stream-tonight.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/Soundsational_Tink.jpg" alt="Soundsational Tink.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;We just wanted to remind you one more time about the live streaming event tonight presented by the &lt;a href="http://disneyparks.disney.go.com/blog"&gt;Disney Parks Blog&lt;/a&gt;. Starting at 4:30pm Pacific (7:20pm Eastern), they will be presenting &lt;em&gt;Mickey’s Soundsational Parade&lt;/em&gt;, live from Disneyland!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;For those who have never seen &lt;em&gt;Mickey’s Soundsational Parade&lt;/em&gt;, it is a highly energetic, musical celebration that starts in Fantasyland (near &lt;em&gt;it’s a small world&lt;/em&gt;) and moves down Main Street U.S.A., led by none other than Mickey Mouse playing drums on the lead float. It includes several beloved Disney characters including Peter Pan, Tinkerbell, Aurora, Cinderella, Belle, Rapunzel, Aladdin, the Genie, Tiana, Simba, and Mary Poppins. You won’t want to miss it!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Check back here closer to show time for any updates. And please leave a comment below letting us know what you think about &lt;em&gt;Mickey’s Soundsational Parade&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;UPDATE: Here’s the link to the YouTube stream (it should become live just before the streaming event starts): &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/embed/oLZwaVr-QEs" class="bare"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/embed/oLZwaVr-QEs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disneyland</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/24/Mickeys-Soundsational-Parade-live-stream-tonight.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luigi's Rollickin' Roadsters to open on March 7</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/25/Luigis-Rollickin-Roadsters-to-open-on-March-7.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/Luigis.jpg" alt="Luigis.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Disney is reporting that Luigi and Guido are returning from their trip to Italy and reopening Casa Della Tires in Disney California Adventure’s Cars Land. When it reopens on March 7th, so will &lt;em&gt;Luigi’s Rollickin' Roadsters&lt;/em&gt;, a trackless family ride where each car will have it’s own unique "dance" so that no two rides will be the same.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;When Cars Land opened in 2012, Casa Della Tires was the home to &lt;em&gt;Luigi’s Flying Tires&lt;/em&gt;, a ride where guests would ride tires on a cushion of air (think really big air hockey table). This was a throwback an early Disneyland attraction, &lt;em&gt;Flying Saucers&lt;/em&gt; in Tomorrowland. Unfortunately, the ride system relied heavily on guests actively leaning in different directions to move the tires and many (especially smaller children) had a difficult time moving the vehicles. So while Luigi and Guido went home to Italy, Disney Imagineers replaced it with &lt;em&gt;Luigi’s Rollickin' Roadsters&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;What do you think about this change? Will you miss &lt;em&gt;Luigi’s Flying Tires&lt;/em&gt;? Or are you looking forward to &lt;em&gt;Luigi’s Rollickin' Roadsters&lt;/em&gt;? Leave a comment and let us know!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disneyland</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/25/Luigis-Rollickin-Roadsters-to-open-on-March-7.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demand pricing expected at Disney World and Disneyland</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/26/Demand-pricing-expected-at-Disney-World-and-Disneyland.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/DL_TicketBooth.jpg" alt="DL TicketBooth.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;If you’re thinking about going to Disney World or Disneyland this year, you should consider getting your tickets &lt;em&gt;NOW&lt;/em&gt;. It’s been rumored for quite awhile and today we’ve heard from several sources that Disney will introduce demand pricing, based on expected crowd levels, very soon (possibly this weekend).&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The idea is that there are times of the year that the parks are busier than other times. During those times, with demand high, admission prices will be higher than on slower days. This is a good-news/bad-news proposition for guests. In theory, it may help even out the crowds, making some of the busier days less busy (while making some of the slower days busier). But it also means that if you want to visit Disney on a busy day, it may cost you more.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Demand pricing is not unusual in the travel industry. Airlines, hotels, and other resorts have employed it for years. Recently, Universal Studios Hollywood introduced demand pricing. And when Shanghai Disneyland opens this summer, it is expected to sell tickets with demand pricing.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The details of this new plan are still unknown. It’s unclear what effect, if any, it will have on tickets purchased as part of vacation packages. Stay tuned to this blog and we’ll update you as soon as we find out more. In the meantime, you may want to consider getting your tickets/vacation booked ASAP. May we suggest that you contact raymie@simplymagicalvacations (or click on the banner at the bottom of this page)?&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;What do you think of Disney’s plan to introduce demand pricing?&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/26/Demand-pricing-expected-at-Disney-World-and-Disneyland.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Friday Favorites! What is your favorite parade in Disney World or Disneyland?</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/26/Friday-Favorites-What-is-your-favorite-parade-in-Disney-World-or-Disneyland.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/FF_Parade.png" alt="FF Parade.png"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Earlier this week, we had a chance to watch &lt;em&gt;Mickey’s Soundsational Parade&lt;/em&gt;, live streamed from Disneyland. And this past Sunday night, we got a glimpse of Disneyland’s &lt;em&gt;Paint the Night Parade&lt;/em&gt; while watching &lt;em&gt;Wonderful World of Disney: Disneyland 60&lt;/em&gt; on ABC. No doubt, Disney knows how to put on a parade!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;So this week, we wanted to ask you which of Disney’s parades is your favorite? Does your foot tap along to the beat in &lt;em&gt;Mickey’s Soundsational Parade&lt;/em&gt;? Do you prefer the classic &lt;em&gt;Main Street Electrical Parade&lt;/em&gt;? Maybe it’s the wondrous and wonderful &lt;em&gt;Disney’s Festival of Fantasy Parade&lt;/em&gt; in the Magic Kingdom. How about the &lt;em&gt;Pixar Play Parade&lt;/em&gt; in Disney California Adventure? Or does &lt;em&gt;Paint the Night&lt;/em&gt; leaving you asking "When can we do this again?"?&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Since there are only a handful of parades currently running in Disney’s U.S. parks, feel free to suggest a retired parade or a parade from one of Disney’s parks in Paris, Tokyo, or Hong Kong. So if you loved &lt;em&gt;Spectromagic&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Tapestry of Nations&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Mickey’s Jammin' Jungle Parade&lt;/em&gt;, or Tokyo’s &lt;em&gt;Dreamlights&lt;/em&gt;, we want to hear from you!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Which Disney parade is your favorite? Leave a comment below and let us know. And don’t forget to tell your friends, neighbors, family, electrician, plumber, and everyone in the theater the next time you go see a movie, to come follow MouseGuests and join in on the fun!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Friday Favorites</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/26/Friday-Favorites-What-is-your-favorite-parade-in-Disney-World-or-Disneyland.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Table service dining coming to Diamond Horseshoe</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/26/Table-service-dining-coming-to-Diamond-Horseshoe.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/DiamondHorseshoe.jpg" alt="DiamondHorseshoe.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The Diamond Horseshoe in Disney World’s Magic Kingdom was an opening day dining location, as the east-coast equivalent of Disneyland’s Golden Horseshoe. But it has been only open rarely in the past dozen or so years. It has been used occasionally as overflow for Liberty Tree Tavern (which it shares a kitchen with) or as quick service, but many times we’ve walked by, it has been closed.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;That changes on March 13th!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Disney has announced that the Diamond Horseshoe will start serving both lunch and dinner as table service dining options. Guests dining at the Diamond Horseshoe will feast on an all-you-care-to-enjoy meal that starts with a Frontier Salad and cornbread, giving way to a choice of BBQ pulled turkey over cornbread, spit-roasted ham and country beans, or stewed beef with mashed potatoes. The dessert course will be a choice of an apple tart or a Campfire Brownie. The meal will be fixed price at $33 plus tax for adults or $19 for children ages 3-9.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;What do you think of this new addition to the Magic Kingdom’s dining lineup? Leave a comment and let us know!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/26/Table-service-dining-coming-to-Diamond-Horseshoe.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney announces price increase and seasonal pricing on 1-day tickets</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/27/Disney-announces-price-increase-and-seasonal-pricing-on-1-day-tickets.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/DL_TicketBooth.jpg" alt="DL TicketBooth.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;We reported yesterday that Disney is expected to introduce seasonal pricing (or demand pricing) this weekend. And now it is official. Starting tomorrow, 1-day tickets will be priced seasonally, based on demand. Disney presents this as a way to spread the crowds out, lowering the crowds on peak days by giving a pricing incentive to go on what are typically slower days.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The way it will work is that each month will have days that are designated as value, regular, and peak days. A 1-day ticket purchased for a value day will be less expensive than for a regular day which will be cheaper than for a peak day. It’s our understanding that 1-day Magic Kingdom ticket prices will be $124 for peak days, $110 for regular days, and $105 for value days, as compared to the current 1-day ticket price of $105. For the other parks in Disney World, the prices will be $114 (peak), $102 (regular), and $97 (value), as compared to the current 1-day ticket price of $97.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;As for Disneyland, the new price points for 1-day tickets will be $119 (peak), $105 (regular), and $95 (value), as compared to the current $99 price for 1-day tickets.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;We believe that seasonal pricing will have little effect on Walt Disney World guests, as those visiting Disney World typically purchase multi-day packages as part of a vacation package. Disneyland guests, on the other hand, are more likely to be impacted as many visitors to Disney’s west coast parks buy one day tickets, either because they’re locals or because they bunch their Disneyland trip in with other activities in the area.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;In addition, tickets prices are expected to go up tomorrow as well on both 1-day and multi-day ticket packages. We do not yet know the new price points, but stay tuned to this blog and we’ll update you as soon as we know more.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;If you’re planning a Disney World or Disneyland trip this year and have not yet purchased tickets or booked your vacation, we recommend you take care of that today before the prices go up. And in all cases, we advise that you always consider buying multi-day ticket packages as those will not be affected by seasonal pricing and the per-day price will be cheaper as you add more days. We recommend that you contact &lt;a href="mailto:raymie@simplymagicalvacations.com"&gt;raymie@simplymagicalvacations.com&lt;/a&gt; or by calling 214-236-7739 to get a free quote on your Disney vacation and snag those tickets before the prices go up.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;What do you think of seasonal pricing? Will this have an impact on a Disney trip you have in your future? Leave a comment and let us know!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/27/Disney-announces-price-increase-and-seasonal-pricing-on-1-day-tickets.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing Disney's new ticket prices</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/28/Analyzing-Disneys-new-ticket-prices.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/DL_TicketBooth.jpg" alt="DL TicketBooth.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Disney’s new ticket prices take effect today, including seasonal pricing for 1-day tickets. What does it mean and how will it impact your pocketbook when you buy tickets?&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;As we reported yesterday, the price for 1-day tickets will vary, depending on when you go, what park(s) you want to visit, and whether or not you buy the Park Hopper option. Suppose you want to go to the Magic Kingdom today. Today is considered a "Value" day, so the price of a 1-day ticket to the Magic Kingdom will be $105. If, however, you want to visit the Magic Kingdom next Sunday, which is a "Regular" day, the price goes up to $110. And most of the later portion of March is categorized as a "Peak" day, taking the price up to $124.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;On the other hand, should you want to visit Epcot, Hollywood Studios, or Animal Kingdom today, the price will be $97. Next Sunday it will be $102. And later in March it will go up to $114.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;If you want to be flexible and get the Park Hopper option, Value days will cost you $155, Regular days will be $160, and Peak days will ring up at $164, per 1-day ticket.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;But if you’re going to visit the parks for more than one day, then multi-day tickets are more economical and are not subject to seasonal pricing. And it gets cheaper per day as you add more days, with a 10-day ticket, without Park Hopper, being the cheapest per-day price point at $40 per day (before tax). The following table describes the prices for multi-day adult tickets (before tax):&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;table class="tableblock frame-all grid-all spread"&gt; 
 &lt;colgroup&gt; 
  &lt;col style="width: 33%;"&gt; 
  &lt;col style="width: 33%;"&gt; 
  &lt;col style="width: 33%;"&gt; 
 &lt;/colgroup&gt; 
 &lt;thead&gt; 
  &lt;tr&gt; 
   &lt;th class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;Days&lt;/th&gt; 
   &lt;th class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;w/o Park Hpper&lt;/th&gt; 
   &lt;th class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;w/Park Hopper&lt;/th&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt; 
 &lt;/thead&gt; 
 &lt;tbody&gt; 
  &lt;tr&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$202.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$257.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt; 
  &lt;tr&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;3&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$290.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$345.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt; 
  &lt;tr&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;4&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$325.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$395.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt; 
  &lt;tr&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;5&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$340.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$409.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt; 
  &lt;tr&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;6&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$355.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$424.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt; 
  &lt;tr&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;7&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$370.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$439.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt; 
  &lt;tr&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;8&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$380.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$449.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt; 
  &lt;tr&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;9&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$390.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$459.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt; 
  &lt;tr&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;10&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$400.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$469.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt; 
 &lt;/tbody&gt; 
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;To give you an idea of how this compares to multi-day prices before the price increase, we compared a multi-day ticket that we purchased before the price increase vs. what one would cost today. We paid $403.64 (incl. tax) for a 5-day ticket with Park Hopper a few weeks ago. Today that same ticket costs $435.59 (incl. tax) for a price difference of $31.95.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;What’s even more economical, it seems, is that if you buy multi-day tickets as part of a resort package (e.g., you stay at a Disney resort on property), the prices are even less expensive. A cursory review suggests that multi-day tickets with a resort package have not gone up at all.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;As for the effect on Disneyland prices, 1-day tickets will be priced at $95 for Value days, $105 for Regular days, and $119 for Peak days. Multi-day adult tickets are priced as follows (before tax):&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;table class="tableblock frame-all grid-all spread"&gt; 
 &lt;colgroup&gt; 
  &lt;col style="width: 33%;"&gt; 
  &lt;col style="width: 33%;"&gt; 
  &lt;col style="width: 33%;"&gt; 
 &lt;/colgroup&gt; 
 &lt;thead&gt; 
  &lt;tr&gt; 
   &lt;th class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;Days&lt;/th&gt; 
   &lt;th class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;w/o Park Hpper&lt;/th&gt; 
   &lt;th class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;w/Park Hopper&lt;/th&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt; 
 &lt;/thead&gt; 
 &lt;tbody&gt; 
  &lt;tr&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$195.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$235.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt; 
  &lt;tr&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;3&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$255.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$295.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt; 
  &lt;tr&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;4&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$280.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$320.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt; 
  &lt;tr&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;5&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$295.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;td class="tableblock halign-left valign-top"&gt;&lt;p class="tableblock"&gt;$335.00&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt; 
 &lt;/tbody&gt; 
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;This makes the cheapest per-day price point for a Disneyland ticket $59 for a 5-day ticket without Park Hopper. (Disneyland doesn’t offer multi-day tickets for more than 5 days.)&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Disney is presenting this as a means of evening out crowd levels across the calender, giving a financial incentive to go during non-peak times. If it works, then the crazy holiday crowds seen around Christmas and Easter may be more tolerable, while non-peak days will become more crowded. If it doesn’t work, then guests buying 1-day tickets will be paying more to visit on days when the crowd levels will make it difficult to get their money’s worth; and those buying 1-day tickets for Value days will be paying less to have more room to move about.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;How do you feel about seasonal pricing? Do you think it will spread the crowds out more? Would you be willing to pay the Peak day prices for a single-day ticket? Or does it not matter to you because you’ll only ever buy multi-day tickets? Leave a comment below and let’s discuss it!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/02/28/Analyzing-Disneys-new-ticket-prices.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More magic coming to MyMagic+</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/01/More-magic-coming-to-MyMagic.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/MagicBands.jpg" alt="MagicBands.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Disney is expected to roll out two new features to MyMagic+ this Spring, including one that it seems &lt;em&gt;everyone&lt;/em&gt; has been asking for.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Currently, Walt Disney World guests are able to pre-select up to 3 attractions per day for FastPass+ (a benefit that lets you skip past the longer standby lines for many attractions). After having used those initial 3 FastPass+ selections, you can go to one of several kiosks in the parks and choose another FastPass+ option (and again until the day is over for additional FastPass+ choices). But in April guests will be able to use the My Disney Experience mobile app to make those additional selections right where they are at without having to wait in line at a kiosk.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The ability to select additional FastPass+ choices from the My Disney Experience app is a long overdue feature of the app. Many times the lines at the kiosks are longer than the standby lines for some of the attractions. And since you don’t even know what’s available until you get to a kiosk, you may have waited in line for nothing. We’ll certainly be making use of this on our next trip.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Additionally, Disney is expected to roll out StoryMaker, a feature of MyMagic+ that offers even greater interactivity in attractions and meet-n-greets. Using long-range RFID in MagicBands (the same way that on-ride photos are automatically linked to a guests My Disney Experience account now), a ride may know who a person is and where they are visiting from to "interact" with them. You may have noticed that some of the signs in the "Goodbye" room on &lt;em&gt;"it’s a small world"&lt;/em&gt; have been replaced with what appear to be TV monitors. Presumably, guests riding &lt;em&gt;"it’s a small world"&lt;/em&gt; will be greeted by name on those monitors as they pass through the "Goodbye" room. Similarly, meet-n-greet characters may greet a guest by name. Imagine walking up to Mickey Mouse and having him greet your personally by name!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;What do you think of these new MyMagic+ features? Leave a comment and let us know.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/01/More-magic-coming-to-MyMagic.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epcot International Flower and Garden Festival blooms today!</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/02/Epcot-International-Flower-and-Garden-Festival-blooms-today.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/MickeyTopiary.jpg" alt="MickeyTopiary.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;One of the most colorful times of the year blooms today at Epcot: The Epcot International Flower and Garden Festival!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Between now and May 30th, visitors to Epcot will experience a landscape that has come alive with colorful flowers and topiaries designed after beloved Disney and Pixar characters. If you have (or desire to have) a green thumb, there will also be gardening experts on-hand, giving tips on gardening at the festival center. And since gardening can build up an appetite, there are over a dozen outdoor kitchens setup around World Showcase, offering specialty dishes, desserts, and drinks.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;On the weekends, catch the rhythms and sounds of Garden Rocks Concert Series at the America Gardens Theater. This year, the concert series features:&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="ulist"&gt; 
 &lt;ul&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;March 4-6: The Orchestra starring former members of ELO&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;March 11-13: STARSHIP featuring Mickey Thomas&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;March 18-20: Little River Band&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;March 25-27: Village People&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;April 1-3: Herman’s Hermits starring Peter Noone&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;April 8-10: The Guess Who&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;April 15-17: Blood, Sweat, and Tears starring Bo Bice&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;April 22-24: Bad Company starring Brian Howe&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;April 29-May 1: Georgia Satellits&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;May 6-8: Gin Blossoms&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;May 13-15: Darlene Love&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;May 20-22: Night Ranger&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;May 27-30: The Spinners&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;/ul&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;That’s three months full of flowers, food, and music to take in when visiting Epcot!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Who’s going to be in Epcot during the Flower and Garden Festival this year? We’re going to be there one of those weekends, for sure. The last time we went we had lots of fun seeking out the topiaries. What are you looking forward to at this year’s festival? Leave a comment and let us know!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/02/Epcot-International-Flower-and-Garden-Festival-blooms-today.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"Finding Dory" characters joining Crush at Turtle Talk with Crush this summer</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/02/Finding-Dory-characters-joining-Crush-at-Turtle-Talk-with-Crush-this-summer.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/TurtleTalk.jpg" alt="TurtleTalk.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;New characts from Pixar’s "Finding Dory" will be swimming up to the "Human Tank" this summer at &lt;em&gt;Turtle Talk with Crush&lt;/em&gt; in both Epcot and Disney California Adventure. The new characters will include Destiny the whale shark, Bailey the beluga whale, and Hank the "septopus". Even the little dude, Squirt, will be joining his old man to answer questions from the humans.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;In case you’re unfamiliar with &lt;em&gt;Turtle Talk with Crush&lt;/em&gt;, it’s a wonderfully fun interactive show where Crush from "Finding Nemo" interacts with the audience (mostly the younger dudes, but sometimes their parentals) answering questions about marine life and asking a few questions he has about human life.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Have you ever been to &lt;em&gt;Turtle Talk with Crush&lt;/em&gt;? What do you think of adding these new characters to the show? Leave a comment and let us know.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/02/Finding-Dory-characters-joining-Crush-at-Turtle-Talk-with-Crush-this-summer.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rivers of Light to debut April 22 in Disney's Animal Kingdom</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/02/Rivers-of-Light-to-debut-April-22-in-Disneys-Animal-Kingdom.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/riversoflight.jpg" alt="riversoflight.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;After many months of anticipation, Disney has confirmed that the new &lt;em&gt;Rivers of Light&lt;/em&gt; nighttime spectacular will debut in Disney’s Animal Kingdom on April 22.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;This all new show, which takes place on the Discovery River between &lt;em&gt;Expedition Everest&lt;/em&gt; and the &lt;em&gt;Tree of Life&lt;/em&gt; will use water screen projections, lanterns, and projections on the &lt;em&gt;Tree of Life&lt;/em&gt; and surrounding landscape to tell a story of four animal Spirit Guides. Based on concept art and some sneak peaks offered by Disney Imagineers, this appears to be a nighttime spectacular on the same level as &lt;em&gt;World of Color&lt;/em&gt; in Disney California Adventure.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The April 22nd debut date is significant in that it is recognized as both Earth Day and as the 18th anniversary of Disney’s Animal Kingdom. And, we’re quite excited about &lt;em&gt;Rivers of Light&lt;/em&gt; debuting on this date, as it is a full week before we make our next visit to Disney World and so we will be able to see this new show shortly after it opens!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;What do you think about &lt;em&gt;Rivers of Light&lt;/em&gt; and the other nighttime activities coming to Disney’s Animal Kingdom in 2016? Leave a comment and let’s discuss!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/02/Rivers-of-Light-to-debut-April-22-in-Disneys-Animal-Kingdom.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Cruise Line to expand to six ships by 2023</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/03/Disney-Cruise-Line-to-expand-to-six-ships-by-2023.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/DCL202123.jpg" alt="DCL202123.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;In Disney’s annual shareholder’s meeting this morning (and then quickly followed by the &lt;a href="http://disneyparks.disney.go.com/blog/"&gt;Disney Parks Blog&lt;/a&gt;), Bob Iger confirmed that two new ships will be added to the Disney Cruise Line fleet. The first will come in 2021 and the next in 2023.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Our first thought was "What will they be named?" So far, no names have been revealed…​but we’ll keep you posted.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Have you ever taken a cruise on a Disney ship? If so, leave a comment and let us know what you thought about it. And let us know what you think of the expansion of Disney’s fleet!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney Cruise Line</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/03/Disney-Cruise-Line-to-expand-to-six-ships-by-2023.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Friday Favorites! What is your favorite character topiary at the Epcot International Flower &amp; Garden Festival?</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/04/Friday-Favorites-What-is-your-favorite-character-topiary-at-the-Epcot-International-Flower-and-Garden-Festival.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/FF_Topiaries_sm.png" alt="FF Topiaries sm.png"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The weather is getting warmer, the days are getting longer, and the trees and flowers are coming to life. That can only mean one thing: It’s time for the Epcot International Flower &amp;amp; Garden Festival! One of our favorite things about the Flower &amp;amp; Garden Festival is all of the topiaries spread around Epcot that resemble Disney characters. This year, the festival runs for 3 months and there are over 3 dozen topiaries, including a brand new Ranger Mickey topiary to celebrate the centennial anniversary of the National Parks Service!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;So this week, we’re asking you which of the Flower &amp;amp; Garden topiaries is your favorite? Do you whistle while you walk past Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs topiaries in the Germany Pavilion? Do the Lady and the Tramp topiaries in the Italy Pavilion make it a bella notte? Do the Cinderella and Prince Charming topiaries in the France Pavilion make you dance?&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Leave us a comment and let us know which topiary is your favorite? If you’ve never been to Epcot during the International Flower &amp;amp; Garden Festival, then search the web for photos of the topiaries (there are lots, including on our &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/mouseguests/"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;) and pick your favorite. And don’t garden alone: Invite your friends, family, neighbors, horticulturist, everyone at the local nursery, and any lawn maintenance crew you see to come check out MouseGuests and join in on the conversation!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Friday Favorites</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/04/Friday-Favorites-What-is-your-favorite-character-topiary-at-the-Epcot-International-Flower-and-Garden-Festival.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Frozen musical opening in Disney California Adventure May 27</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/04/New-Frozen-musical-opening-in-Disney-California-Adventure-May-27.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/FrozenHyperion.jpg" alt="FrozenHyperion.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Earlier this year, we sadly said goodbye to &lt;em&gt;Aladdin: A Musical Spectacular&lt;/em&gt; in Disney California Adventure’s Hyperion Theater. But coming May 27th, you’ll be able to see &lt;em&gt;Frozen - Live at the Hyperion&lt;/em&gt; an all new musical adaptation of the popular Disney film &lt;em&gt;Frozen&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Disney promises elaborate costumes, sets, special effects, puppetry, and music to make this a must-see show. If it’s anything nearly as good as its predecessor, it will be amazing.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Disney has also announced that with the new &lt;em&gt;Frozen&lt;/em&gt; show opening in the Hyperion Theater, &lt;em&gt;For the First Time in Forever: A Frozen Sing-Along Celebration&lt;/em&gt; will be closing on April 17th. We’re hopeful that this means that &lt;em&gt;Muppet*Vision 3D&lt;/em&gt; will be returning to Disney California Adventure shortly thereafter.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Are you excited to see &lt;em&gt;Frozen - Live at the Hyperion&lt;/em&gt;? Do you think it will match up to &lt;em&gt;Aladdin: A Musical Spectacular&lt;/em&gt;? Leave a comment below and let us know!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disneyland</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/04/New-Frozen-musical-opening-in-Disney-California-Adventure-May-27.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Purple MagicBands now a choice in MyMagic+</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/06/Purple-MagicBands-now-a-choice-in-MyMagic.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/PurpleMagicBand.png" alt="PurpleMagicBand.png"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Purple MagicBand fans rejoice! Purple is now an option in MyMagic+!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;When MagicBands were first introduced over 3 years ago, they came in a handful of colors such as red, yellow, orange, green, blue, and pink. But purple was strangely missing from that list. And it has been one of the most requested MagicBand colors ever since. Recently, purple MagicBands have been available for a cost, but they still weren’t available as one of the free choices when planning a Disney World vacation.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Are you excited about the addition of purple to the MagicBand lineup? If you could add another color choice, what would pick? Leave a comment and let us know.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/06/Purple-MagicBands-now-a-choice-in-MyMagic.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Captain America and Spider Man to meet Disney California Adventure Guests</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/07/Captain-America-and-Spider-Man-to-meet-Disney-California-Adventure-Guests.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/CaptainAmerica.jpg" alt="CaptainAmerica.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The First Avenger and your friendly neighborhood webslinger are scheduled to start meeting guests in Disney California Adventure starting April 3rd. This also marks a move of Disneyland’s Marvel presence to Disney California Adventure as Marvel HQ is set to close on April 2.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;For the past couple of years, Disneyland guests have been able to virtually suit up in Tony Stark’s Iron Man suit, see a collection of Iron Man suits, and cross the bifrost to meet Thor in Disneyland’s Tomorrowland. But now it seems that the second floor of the former Innoventions building (which also once housed the Carousel of Progress and America Sings) will be taking on a new tenant.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;We can’t help but wonder what this means, both for the Innoventions building as well as for Marvel’s presence at the Disneyland Resort. There have been rumors for awhile that Disney California Adventure would someday be expanded with a Marvel-themed area. Could this be a first small move in that direction? And what will become of the Innoventions building? Will Star Wars Launch Bay expand to the second floor or does Disney have other plans for the space?&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;What do you think of this move? Leave a comment and let’s discuss it!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disneyland</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/07/Captain-America-and-Spider-Man-to-meet-Disney-California-Adventure-Guests.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Be an armchair imagineer in "Disney Magic Kingdoms" coming soon!</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/08/Be-an-armchair-imagineer-in-Disney-Magic-Kingdoms-coming-soon.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/DisneyMagicKingdoms.png" alt="DisneyMagicKingdoms.png"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;If you’ve ever wanted to build your own Disney theme park, your chance is coming soon. Disney Games released a new trailer video for "Disney Magic Kingdoms"!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="videoblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;iframe width="500" height="281" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/VsnnUtoqCV8?rel=0&amp;amp;list=" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;This park-building game was announced at last year’s D23, but there has been nothing but silence about the game since then. With the release of this trailer, we’re hoping to be building our own Magic Kingdom on our mobile devices very soon. This looks like a lot of fun!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;"Disney Magic Kingdoms" will be available for iOS, Android, and Windows Phone (in each device’s respective app store).&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;How are you going to design your Disney theme park? Leave a comment and let us know!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/08/Be-an-armchair-imagineer-in-Disney-Magic-Kingdoms-coming-soon.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joy and Sadness to meet in expanded Epcot Character Spot next month</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/09/Joy-and-Sadness-to-meet-in-expanded-Epcot-Character-Spot-next-month.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/JoyAndSadness.jpg" alt="JoyAndSadness.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;I suppose that this is bittersweet news: Both Joy and Sadness from Pixar’s "Inside Out" are set to join Baymax in the newly expanded Character Spot in Epcot next month! In case you’ve not seen "Inside Out", Joy and Sadness are two of the emotions that define Riley’s personality, along with Anger, Fear, and Disgust.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Unlike the classic Disney characters that meet in the original Character Spot, there will be no FastPass+ option to meet Baymax or Joy and Sadness. Given the popularity of the movie and the newness of these characters, we expect this to be a very popular meet-n-greet with a long line. If you are hoping to meet them, you’ll want to plan accordingly.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Does this new meet-n-greet give you joy or does it make you sad? Leave us a comment and let us know what you think!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/09/Joy-and-Sadness-to-meet-in-expanded-Epcot-Character-Spot-next-month.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star Wars Day at Sea returning in early 2017</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/10/Star-Wars-Day-at-Sea-returning-in-early-2017.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/StarWarsDayAtSea.jpg" alt="StarWarsDayAtSea.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The force is strong with this cruise.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Star Wars has never been more popular than it is now. And with the success of Star Wars Day at Sea on the Disney Cruise Line this year, Disney has announced that it will return for 2017, expanding to both eastern and western Caribbean 7-night itineraries.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Special activities on the Star Wars Day at Sea include: Star Wars characters on-board for meet-n-greets, Star Wars trivia, Jedi Training, Star Wars-themed arts and crafts, a deck party, fireworks, Star Wars themed food and beverages, and film screenings of all seven Star Wars films plus a screening of the new "Rogue One" movie to be released later this year.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;These Star Wars itineraries are limited to only 15 sailings from early January through mid-April from Port Canaveral. They’re going to be really popular, so I recommend that you book your itinerary as soon as possible. May I also recommend that you contact raymie@simplymagicalvacations (or 214-236-7739) to get started on your Star Wars adventure at sea!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;What do you think of these Star Wars-themed cruise activities? Leave a comment and let us know!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney Cruise</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/10/Star-Wars-Day-at-Sea-returning-in-early-2017.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Should you bother visiting Disney's Hollywood Studios on your next trip?</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/11/Should-you-bother-visiting-Disneys-Hollywood-Studios-on-your-next-trip.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/ChineseTheater.jpg" alt="ChineseTheater.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;In case you’ve missed it, Disney’s Hollywood Studios is undergoing a major overhaul. The original intent for the park was to be a working movie studio, with a few attractions along for the ride. Although a few movies were made at DHS (back when it was Disney-MGM Studios), including Mulan, Lilo &amp;amp; Stitch, Brother Bear, and Ernest Saves Christmas, the plan to have a working studio never panned out. Over time, shows, rides and attractions were added to the park, but the Hollywood theme has been disjointed at best.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;In an effort to correct the issues with DHS, Disney has announced two major new additions to the park: A 14 acre Star Wars-themed land and an 11 acre Toy Story-themed land. There’s also possibility of additional expansion to the park after those two lands are completed. And at last year’s Disney shareholder’s meeting, CEO Bob Iger let it slip that the park would be receiving a new name (it’s third name in its history).&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;With this expansion come some growing pains. Some attractions have closed down and others are slated to be closed soon to make way for the construction of the new lands. Included among the attractions that have gone away in the past few years or are on their way out are:&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="ulist"&gt; 
 &lt;ul&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Studio Backlot Tour&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Lights, Motors, Action&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Magic of Disney Animation&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sounds Dangerous&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The American Idol Experience&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Legend of Jack Sparrow&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Pixar Pals Countdown to Fun&lt;/em&gt; parade&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Mulch, Sweat, &amp;amp; Shears&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Osborne Family Spectacle of Dancing Lights&lt;/em&gt; (seasonal)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Star Wars Weekends&lt;/em&gt; (seasonal)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;The Sorcerer’s Hat (not an attraction, but it is gone)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;/ul&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;In a park that was already thought by some to be a half-day park, and with so many attractions going away, you may be wondering if you should skip Disney’s Hollywood Studios altogether on your next Disney World trip. After all, is there enough still open to fill a day in the park? To answer that question, let’s consider what’s still open:&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="ulist"&gt; 
 &lt;ul&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Indiana Jones Epic Stunt Show&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Star Tours&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Jedi Training Academy&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Muppet*Vision 3D&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Toy Story Midway Mania&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Great Movie Ride&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;One Man’s Dream&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Voyage of the Little Mermaid&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Disney Jr. Live&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Rock 'n' Roller Coaster Starring Aerosmith&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Twilight Zone Tower of Terror&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Beauty and the Beast Live&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Fantasmic!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Citizens of Hollywood (streetmosphere)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Star Wars Launch Bay&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;For the First Time in Forever: A Frozen Sign-Along Celebration&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Symphony in the Stars: A Galactic Spectacular&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;/ul&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Yes, I realize that at least a few of the entries on that list are rumored to be going away soon. But they’re not gone yet, so it’s fair to leave them on this list.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;I know I can’t speak for every Disney World guest, but when I look at the list of recently closed attractions and compare it with the list of attractions still available, I don’t feel as if I’ve lost that much. I will absolutely miss things like &lt;em&gt;The Legend of Jack Sparrow&lt;/em&gt;, Star Wars Weekends, and &lt;em&gt;Mulch, Sweat, &amp;amp; Shears&lt;/em&gt;. And I was there in December to say my final goodbye to the &lt;em&gt;Osborne Family Spectacle of Dancing Lights&lt;/em&gt;. But aside from that, it’s a bunch of stuff that we hardly ever (if ever) visited.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The list of still open attractions, on the other hand, represents many of the reasons we go to Hollywood Studios. They’re still open and we still have a reason to go; even if the rest of the park is behind construction walls for the next couple of years.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;To give you an idea of how we spend a day in Hollywood Studios, what follows is a rough plan we go by:&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="ulist"&gt; 
 &lt;ul&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;Head to &lt;em&gt;Toy Story Midway Mania&lt;/em&gt; at rope drop and ride it from the standby line.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;Turn around and use FastPass+ to ride &lt;em&gt;Toy Story Midway Mania&lt;/em&gt; again.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;Meet-n-greet with Woody and Buzz Lightyear&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Muppet*Vision 3D&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Star Tours&lt;/em&gt;, probably with FastPass+&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;Head back to center stage to see &lt;em&gt;Citizens of Hollywood&lt;/em&gt;'s "Cavalcade of Stars"&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Great Movie Ride&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;Depending on time, maybe walk through &lt;em&gt;One Man’s Dream&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;Lunch, either at &lt;em&gt;Backlot Express&lt;/em&gt; or perhaps &lt;em&gt;50’s Prime Time&lt;/em&gt; or &lt;em&gt;Sci-fi Dine-In&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Indiana Jones Epic Stunt Show&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Voyage of the Little Mermaid&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Star Wars Launch Bay&lt;/em&gt; to meet Darth Vader and Chewbacca (or now it’s Kylo Ren and Chewbacca)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;Take in a few of the &lt;em&gt;Citizens of Hollywood&lt;/em&gt; shows on Sunset and Hollywood Blvds.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;Cupcakes at &lt;em&gt;Starring Rolls&lt;/em&gt; (the Butterfinger cupcake is my favorite)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Twilight Zone Tower of Terror&lt;/em&gt;, probably with FastPass+&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Beauty and the Beast Live&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;Depending on time and the lines, maybe &lt;em&gt;Rock 'n' Roller Coaster Starring Aerosmith&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;See some more &lt;em&gt;Citizens of Hollywood&lt;/em&gt; shows&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dinner (at one of the places we didn’t choose for lunch)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Fantasmic!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;And then finish off with &lt;em&gt;Symphony in the Stars: A Galactic Spectacular&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;/ul&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;This is just a rough plan. Dining reservation times, show times, and FastPass+ return times dictate the exact flow and some adjustment may be necessary. And we might pad some of that time with more character meet-n-greets and shopping.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;I don’t know about you, but that looks like a full day of fun to me. It certainly doesn’t look like the itinerary for a park that is half shutdown. In fact, I think it’d be difficult to fit all of that into a single day at Hollywood Studios. Once the new Star Wars and Toy Story lands open up, it will be impossible to take it all in in a single day.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The point is that even though there’s going to be a lot of construction walls around Hollywood Studios over the next several years, there’s still plenty to do. And the closings that have happened so far are a small price to pay for what promise to be some incredibly immersive new lands in the park.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Even so, I will acknowledge that there’s not much in Hollywood Studios for smaller children (under 5) to enjoy. But this has always been the case and the closings have had little impact on that. Although &lt;em&gt;Disney Jr. Live on Stage&lt;/em&gt; will be about their speed and they may enjoy &lt;em&gt;Toy Story Midway Mania&lt;/em&gt;, height restrictions will keep them from enjoying many of the other attractions in the park. For parents of smaller children, we recommend that you take advantage of Rider Switch to enjoy a few of the key attractions at Hollywood Studios and then use Park Hopper to visit a park that has more for the little ones to enjoy.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;What do you think of the changes taking place in Disney’s Hollywood Studios? Leave a comment and let’s discuss!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/11/Should-you-bother-visiting-Disneys-Hollywood-Studios-on-your-next-trip.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch IllumiNations live on Monday night!</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/18/Watch-IllumiNations-live-on-Monday-night.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/Illuminations.jpg" alt="Illuminations.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;As you probably know, Disney puts on some amazing nighttime shows. And on Monday night (March 21st), you’ll be able to enjoy one of them from the comfort of home. The Disney Parks Blog will be live streaming &lt;em&gt;IllumiNations: Reflections of Earth&lt;/em&gt; on Monday night at 8:50pm (eastern)!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;IllumiNations&lt;/em&gt; is one of Disney’s largest nighttime spectaculars, taking place on Epcot’s World Showcase Lagoon. When viewing &lt;em&gt;IllumiNations&lt;/em&gt; in Epcot, you can see it from almost any location along the 1.2 mile circumference of the lagoon. The show includes fireworks, lasers, fire, and a spinning globe which is actually a spherical video display. Along with a breathtaking musical score composed by Gavin Greenaway, the show takes place in 3 acts: Chaos, Order, and Meaning.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Be sure to tune in to the &lt;a href="https://disneyparks.disney.go.com/blog/"&gt;Disney Parks Blog&lt;/a&gt; on Monday evening to watch the &lt;em&gt;IllumiNations&lt;/em&gt; live streaming event. You don’t want to miss it! We’ll post more information about the show on Monday as it becomes available.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Are you excited to watch the &lt;em&gt;IllumiNations&lt;/em&gt; live streaming event on Monday night? Leave a comment and let us know!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/18/Watch-IllumiNations-live-on-Monday-night.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney After Hours coming to Magic Kingdom</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/21/Disney-After-Hours-coming-to-Magic-Kingdom.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/CastleAtDusk.jpg" alt="CastleAtDusk.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;How much would you pay to stay a few extra hours in the Magic Kingdom after the park closes to ride a few more rides and meet a few more characters? If you’re willing to shell out $149 per person, then you may be interested in &lt;em&gt;Magic Kingdom: Disney After Hours&lt;/em&gt;, a new hard-ticket event coming to the Magic Kingdom for 7 nights in April and May.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Think of it as &lt;em&gt;Mickey’s Not-So Scary Halloween Party&lt;/em&gt; or &lt;em&gt;Mickey’s Very Merry Christmas Party&lt;/em&gt;, only without the Halloween or Christmas party aspect. Or like evening Extra Magic Hours for anyone (including guests not staying in a Disney resort) willing to pay extra. Tickets are set to go on sale April 6th for the after hours event on Aprili 14th, 21th, and 28th and May 5th, 8th, 12th, and 19th.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;What do you think of this new after-hour event? Is this something you’d be willing to pay extra for? Or do you think Disney is trying this out to see if they can do away with Extra Magic Hours free to resort guests? Leave a comment and let us know!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/21/Disney-After-Hours-coming-to-Magic-Kingdom.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FastPass+ no longer offered for Magic Kingdom parades and fireworks</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/22/FastPass-no-longer-offered-for-Magic-Kingdom-parades-and-fireworks.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/FoF_Dragon2.jpg" alt="FoF Dragon2.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Visitors to Walt Disney World’s Magic Kingdom will no longer be able to use FastPass+ to secure prime locations for viewing &lt;em&gt;Festival of Fantasy Parade&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;The Main Street Electrical Parade&lt;/em&gt;, or &lt;em&gt;Wishes&lt;/em&gt;. If you want to see these shows, you’ll need to stake out a spot without the help of the FastPass+ system.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;And this is just fine with us. Although we’ve used FastPass+ once for viewing &lt;em&gt;Festival of Fantasy&lt;/em&gt;, we found that it wasn’t very useful. Even with FastPass+, it helped to show up 30 minutes or more before the show started…​at which time other great spots could also be had without FastPass+. Moreover, using FastPass+ for the nighttime shows would tie up your last FastPass+ selection, preventing you from obtaining additional selections at the kiosks (or coming soon, in the My Disney Experience app).&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;If you’re looking for the best viewing for either of the Magic Kingdom parades, we recommend that you look for a location on the west side of the hub, between the Liberty Square bridge and the &lt;em&gt;Partners&lt;/em&gt; statue. The parades will go past this spot and shortly before the parade comes by, cast members will run a rope between the bridge and the hub. You’ll want to be just inside of where that rope will be to get a great view of either parade. Alternatively, if you’re running a bit late to catch that spot, there are also some great spots in Liberty Square and Frontierland. Just look for the areas on the ground that are taped off and find one that lets you stand just inside of the tape.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;For Wishes, the best location is from the lift hill on &lt;em&gt;Big Thunder Mountain&lt;/em&gt;. But since that requires careful timing and you won’t be able to see the entire show, you might want to find any spot near the hub, south of the &lt;em&gt;Parters&lt;/em&gt; statue. Avoid getting too close to the castle or else it will block your view of some of the fireworks. The platform at the Main Street train station is also a good location for viewing &lt;em&gt;Wishes&lt;/em&gt;. And for something entirely different, consider viewing the fireworks from a boat on &lt;em&gt;Ferrytale Wishes Dessert Cruise&lt;/em&gt; or &lt;em&gt;Pirates and Pals Fireworks Voyage&lt;/em&gt;. We’ve taken the &lt;em&gt;Pirates and Pals Fireworks Voyage&lt;/em&gt; and can say it’s a lot of fun and has a magnificent view of &lt;em&gt;Wishes&lt;/em&gt; from the Seven Seas Lagoon.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;What do you think of FastPass+ going away for the Magic Kingdom parades and fireworks? What’s your favorite spot to view these shows from? Leave us a comment and share your thoughts!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/22/FastPass-no-longer-offered-for-Magic-Kingdom-parades-and-fireworks.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Star-Lord checking in at the Hollywood Tower Hotel?</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/23/Is-Star-Lord-checking-in-at-the-Hollywood-Tower-Hotel.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/ToT.jpg" alt="ToT.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;In case you’ve missed it, there’s a disturbing rumor circulating this week that Disney is planning on introducing "Guardians of the Galaxy" to Disney’s Hollywood Studios and Disney California Adventure. The disturbing part of the rumor is that it will come in the form of a re-theme of the &lt;em&gt;Twilight Zone Tower of Terror&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;I thought "Guardians of the Galaxy" was a great movie and I’d love to see more of it (and other Marvel properties) represented in Disney’s parks. However, re-theming the &lt;em&gt;Tower of Terror&lt;/em&gt; would be tragic.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The &lt;em&gt;Tower of Terror&lt;/em&gt; (speaking primarily of the version in Disney’s Hollywood Studios) is a masterpiece, one of the few attractions that undisputedly qualify as E-Tickets. From Epcot’s World Showcase, the architecture of the &lt;em&gt;Tower of Terror&lt;/em&gt; blends in perfectly as the backdrop of the Morocco Pavilion. From within Disney’s Hollywood Studios, the ominous towering structure draws you closer as you look down Sunset Blvd. As you approach the hotel and enter its queue, the gardens and dry fountains will have you believe that you are actually standing outside of a long-abandoned hotel.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Upon walking into the lobby, the background music and exquisitly detailed theming drive home that belief. The "Out of Order" sign on the elevator door suggests that something unusual has happened here and that you should not venture further. But of course, you do, stepping into the library only to have your heart stop as the thunder cracks and the lights go dim. After Rod Serling establishes the backstory, you step through the boiler room with dim lighting and eery sounds that raise your anxiety.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Once aboard the elevator, the ride itself is magnificent. First you see an endless hallway with ghosts of hotel guests beckoning you to join them. That hallway fades into a starfield, with only a distant window remaining…​until it shatters. Upon arriving at the "5th dimension", the most uncommon elevator leaves the elevator shaft and moves horizontally through strange sights and sounds.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Finally, the elevator drops only to rise again and drop several more times. After the elevator comes to a rest, you are given a warm welcome back by the voice of Rod Serling and a word of warning to be careful about checking into an abandoned hotel on the dark side of Hollywood.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The &lt;em&gt;Tower of Terror&lt;/em&gt; debuted in Disney’s Hollywood Studios nearly 20 years ago. Although I’ve been a passenger on that most uncommon elevator many times, the ride is still as fresh, exciting, and immersive as it was when I first stepped through those doors in 1998. It is one of my favorite attractions, not because of the drop sequence (which is really rather plain compared to the rest of the attraction), but because of the attention to detail and story. It is the ride that first made clear to me that Disney attractions are more about story than a specific ride mechanic.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;While I can imagine that a "Guardians of the Galaxy" re-theme of &lt;em&gt;Tower of Terror&lt;/em&gt; could be good, I struggle imagining it to be as epic as what has stood at the end of Sunset Blvd. for the past 20 years. I wholly support bringing Marvel to the parks, but not at the expense of what is a very popular and thematically perfect attraction.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Again, this opinion is largely applied to the &lt;em&gt;Tower of Terror&lt;/em&gt; in Disney’s Hollywood Studios. I have a similar, but weaker opinion for Disney California Adventure’s &lt;em&gt;Tower of Terror&lt;/em&gt;, which I believe to be the inferior implementation (aside from the mirror effect, which I like a lot).&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;What do you think of this rumor (and I stress again that it is only a rumor at this time)? Would "Guardians of the Galaxy" freshen up the &lt;em&gt;Tower of Terror&lt;/em&gt; in favor of the "Twilight Zone" theme that may be too old and lost on today’s park visitors? Or is the &lt;em&gt;Tower of Terror&lt;/em&gt; a masterpiece that, like da Vinci’s &lt;em&gt;Mona Lisa&lt;/em&gt; or Michaelangelo’s &lt;em&gt;David&lt;/em&gt; should remain untouched? Leave us a comment and let’s discuss.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/23/Is-Star-Lord-checking-in-at-the-Hollywood-Tower-Hotel.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2016 Dates announced for Mickey's Not-So-Scary Halloween Party and Mickey's Very Merry Christmas Party</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/24/2016-Dates-announced-for-Mickeys-Not-So-Scary-Halloween-Party-and-Mickeys-Very-Merry-Christmas-Party.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/MVMCP.jpg" alt="MVMCP.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;There’s no party like a Disney party! And dates for the Magic Kingdom’s two biggest holiday parties, &lt;em&gt;Mickey’s Not-So-Scary Halloween Party&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Mickey’s Very Merry Christmas Party&lt;/em&gt;, have been announced!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;For trick-or-treating fun in the Magic Kingdom this fall, try &lt;em&gt;Mickey’s Not-So-Scary Halloween Party&lt;/em&gt;. In addition to enjoying many of the Magic Kingdom’s fun attractions, you’ll also be able to meet with some unique characters in their Halloween costumes and see the villainous &lt;em&gt;Boo to You&lt;/em&gt; parade! There are also trick-or-treat stations setup around the park for satisfying your sweet tooth! The party dates are: September 2, 8, 11, 13, 16, 18, 20, 23, 25, 29, 30, and October 2, 4, 6, 7, 10, 11, 13, 14, 16, 18, 20, 21, 23, 25, 27, 28, 30, 31.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;For a joyous Christmas celebration, you can also visit &lt;em&gt;Mickey’s Very Merry Christmas Party&lt;/em&gt;. There will be several holiday celebrations, including a special Christmas parade and fireworks show, and meet and greet several characters in their holiday best! You’ll also be able to pick up complimentary cookies at several locations around the Magic Kingdom. The Christmas party takes place on the following dates: November 7, 8, 10, 11, 13, 15, 18, 27, 29, and December 1, 2, 4, 6, 8, 9, 11, 13, 15, 16, 18, 22.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Both of these parties are hard-ticket after-hours events (that is, you must purchase a ticket for the party that is distinct from park admission) and tend to sell out rather quickly. If you think you might want to go to one of these parties, reserve your tickets soon.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;For help in arranging your Halloween or Christmas visit to Walt Disney World, I recommend that you contact &lt;a href="mailto:raymie@simplymagicalvacations.com"&gt;raymie@simplymagicalvacations.com&lt;/a&gt; (or call 214-236-7739). She can make sure you have a magical trip and, as always, her Disney vacation planning services are free to you.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Have you ever been to one of these holiday parties in the Magic Kingdom? Do you think you’d like to go? Leave a comment and let us know what you think!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/03/24/2016-Dates-announced-for-Mickeys-Not-So-Scary-Halloween-Party-and-Mickeys-Very-Merry-Christmas-Party.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREAKING: Disney to offer "Third Shift Magic Hours" after-after-hours event</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/04/01/BREAKING-Disney-to-offer-Third-Shift-Magic-Hours-after-after-hours-event.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/NightCastle.jpg" alt="NightCastle.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;As you may know, Disney has offered Extra Magic Hours for years as a perk to guests staying in a Disney resort. And recently Disney has announced "Disney After Hours", a hard-ticket event that gives visitors access to the Magic Kingdom after the park closes for meeting characters, shorter lines at select attractions, and drinks and ice cream. In addition, we’ve just learned about "Third Shift Magic Hours", a new hard-ticket after-after-hours event coming to the Magic Kingdom.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;"Third Shift Magic Hours" will offer guests a unique opportunity to see the park in ways that virtually nobody ever sees it. Once all of the crowds are gone and the park is completely closed, you’ll be able to participate in unique interactive experiences, including (but not limited to): Mickey’s Custodial Adventure, Stitch’s Street Sweep Sensation, and Pooh’s Potty Purification Parade.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Disney spokesperson, Josh Inyu, tells us that this is a prime example of giving guests what they want: "As we survey Disney World visitors, two themes stand out. Guests want longer hours and want the parks to be clean and well-maintained. This new premium experience addresses both of those concerns."&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;It’s our understanding that while this experience will be initially exclusive to the Magic Kingdom, if successful it may be offered at all Disney parks and resorts.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The price tag for this one of a kind experience is $69, which includes unlimited bottles of water, a grey commemorative jumpsuit, and one-size-fits-all latex gloves. Dates for "Third Shift Magic Hours" will be announced soon. Due to Florida labor laws, "Third Shift Magic Hours" will be limited to visitors 16 years and older.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;And now that April 1 as come and gone, we can now reveal this as an April Fools' joke and not real news. In case it wasn’t obvious.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/04/01/BREAKING-Disney-to-offer-Third-Shift-Magic-Hours-after-after-hours-event.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREAKING NEWS: Guardians of the Galaxy confirmed for Disney's Hollywood Studios</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/04/01/BREAKING-NEWS-Guardians-of-the-Galaxy-confirmed-for-Disneys-Hollywood-Studios.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/GuardiansOfTheTower.jpg" alt="GuardiansOfTheTower.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;In case you missed it, rumors have been circulating for the past few weeks that Disney is planning to retheme the &lt;em&gt;Twilight Zone Tower of Terror&lt;/em&gt; to "Guardians of the Galaxy". Despite overwhelmingly negative response to this rumor, we’ve just learned that Disney is not only moving forward with this move, but that the "Guardians of the Galaxy" plans are far more extensive.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;We reached out to Disney for comment on the supposed plans to retheme the &lt;em&gt;Tower of Terror&lt;/em&gt;. Disney spokesperson, Jessa Keating, confirmed that in addition to retheming the &lt;em&gt;Tower of Terror&lt;/em&gt;, Disney had designs for retheming both Sunset and Hollywood Blvds in support of the upcoming "Guardians of the Galaxy" sequel.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Specifically, the following attractions will be directly impacted:&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="ulist"&gt; 
 &lt;ul&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Tower of Terror&lt;/em&gt; will be reworked as the &lt;em&gt;Tower of Knowhere&lt;/em&gt;. The basic ride system will remain as-is, but instead of a 1930’s Hollywood hotel, the building will be a tower that exists in the fictional "Knowhere" from the GotG comics and movies. We have seen concept art showing the members of the Guardians of the Galaxy beckoning riders to join them in place of the hotel guests from the current version of the ride.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Great Movie Ride&lt;/em&gt; will be renamed &lt;em&gt;The Groot Movie Ride&lt;/em&gt;. Many of the same scenes that exist now will be reworked to include the lovable tree-like alien from GotG. Imagine Gene Kelly "Singin' in the Rain" while swinging from the side of Groot. Or how about the Wicked Groot of the West terrorizing Munchkinland? And the cowboy/gangster switchout portions of the ride will be exchanged for big Groot and a baby dancing Groot.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Rock 'n' Roller Coaster Starring Aerosmith&lt;/em&gt; will be reworked as the &lt;em&gt;Rocket Raccoon Coaster&lt;/em&gt;. Instead of riding a stretch limo through the freeways of L.A., the new &lt;em&gt;Rocket Raccoon Coaster&lt;/em&gt; will take you on a fast-paced ride on the &lt;em&gt;Milano&lt;/em&gt; as it crashes through the &lt;em&gt;Dark Aster&lt;/em&gt;. The soundtrack will include music from "Awesome Mix Vol. 1".&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Fantasmic!&lt;/em&gt; will be replaced by &lt;em&gt;Draxtasmic!&lt;/em&gt;, a musical and visual spectacular that explores the inner-thoughts of Drax the Destroyer as he dreams of revenge on Ronan the Accuser and struggles to understand common idioms as anything other than literal statements.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Beauty and the Beast Live&lt;/em&gt; will be replaced with a musical stage show with a story formula similar to the existing show, except with Gamora, Thanos, and Star-Lord in the roles of Belle, Beast, and Gaston, respectively.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;/ul&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;We were especially confused by the &lt;em&gt;Beauty and the Beast&lt;/em&gt; replacement. Jessa assured us that it’d be a magnificent production, even if budgetary constraints will limit the show to follow the current show’s story line.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Additionally, all of the dining and shopping venues along Sunset and Hollywood Blvds will be reworked to match the new theme. Although Jessa explained that details were still being finalized, she did mention that &lt;em&gt;Reel Vogue&lt;/em&gt; (formerly &lt;em&gt;Villains in Vogue&lt;/em&gt;) will be themed as the Collector’s shop. And she hinted that the popular cupcake source, &lt;em&gt;Starring Rolls&lt;/em&gt;, will be renamed &lt;em&gt;Star-Lord Rolls&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;In related news, Jessa also may have leaked the new name being considered for Disney’s Hollywood Studios. At one point in the conversation, she referred to the park as "Disney’s Star-Lord Wars Muppet Toy Adventure".&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;We have no news on the rumor that the &lt;em&gt;Tree of Life&lt;/em&gt; in Disney’s Animal Kingdom will be replaced with a 199 foot tall Groot.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;And now that April 1 as come and gone, we can now reveal this as an April Fools' joke and not real news. In case it wasn’t obvious.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/04/01/BREAKING-NEWS-Guardians-of-the-Galaxy-confirmed-for-Disneys-Hollywood-Studios.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREAKING NEWS: Super premium parking coming to the Seven Seas Lagoon</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/04/01/BREAKING-NEWS-Super-premium-parking-coming-to-the-Seven-Seas-Lagoon.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/ParkingTram.jpg" alt="ParkingTram.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;You may have already heard that in the past month, Disney has started testing premium parking at the Magic Kingdom. While this test has been received with mixed reviews, Disney has announced that they plan to move forward with what they are calling "Super Premium Magic Parking".&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Currently, guests driving their own vehicles to the Magic Kingdom must park in parking lots that are separated from the Magic Kingdom by the Seven Seas Lagoon. Even with premium parking, a ride on a ferry boat or a monorail separates you from a day in the Magic Kingdom. But with this new super-premium parking option, guests willing to pay $99 per day will be able to position their car as close to the gates as possible.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;According to Newt Riley, our contact at the Magic Kingdom, Disney will provide this new super-premium parking option with plans to fill and pave over the Seven Seas Lagoon. At roughly 175 acres, the space consumed by the Seven Seas Lagoon will offer a tremendous amount of parking for visitors who don’t want to be bothered with riding the ferry boats or monorail from the Transportation and Ticket Center to the front gates.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;For more budget-conscious guests or those who would rather park further away, the remote parking spaces will still be available. Both the monorail and ferry boats will be available to shuttle guests from their remote space to the front gates. The ferries will be reworked to operate on pavement using the same trackless ride technology used in Hong Kong Disneyland’s &lt;em&gt;Mystic Manor&lt;/em&gt; and Tokyo Disneyland’s &lt;em&gt;Pooh’s Hunny Hunt&lt;/em&gt;. A wide path through the premium parking area will be kept clear for the ferry boats to operate.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;And now that April 1 as come and gone, we can now reveal this as an April Fools' joke and not real news. In case it wasn’t obvious.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/04/01/BREAKING-NEWS-Super-premium-parking-coming-to-the-Seven-Seas-Lagoon.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer Awakens at Walt Disney World</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/04/05/Summer-Awakens-at-Walt-Disney-World.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/LaunchBay.jpg" alt="LaunchBay.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The days are getting longer and the temperatures are rising. That can only mean that summer is almost here. And if you’re planning a trip to Walt Disney World, then you’re in for an amazing summer. There are new experiences at all four of Walt Disney’s theme parks, at Disney’s Blizzard Beach water park, and at Disney Springs.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Let’s first take a look at what’s coming to the Magic Kingdom. This past weekend, &lt;em&gt;Dream Along with Mickey&lt;/em&gt; took a final bow to make way for a brand new castle stage show, &lt;em&gt;Mickey’s Royal Friendship Faire&lt;/em&gt;. This new musical adventure will feature characters and music from &lt;em&gt;The Princess and the Frog&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Tangled&lt;/em&gt;, and &lt;em&gt;Frozen&lt;/em&gt;, not to mention Mickey Mouse and friends.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;In Epcot, you’ll want to stop by the Land Pavilion to see the all new &lt;em&gt;Soarin' Over the World&lt;/em&gt;, an update to the original &lt;em&gt;Soarin' Over California&lt;/em&gt; hang glider attraction. Then grab shell and visit with Crush at &lt;em&gt;Turtle Talk with Crush&lt;/em&gt;, updated to include new characters from &lt;em&gt;Finding Dory&lt;/em&gt;. You’ll also want to visit the all new Character Spot featuring Baymax from &lt;em&gt;Big Hero 6&lt;/em&gt; and Joy and Sadness from &lt;em&gt;Inside Out&lt;/em&gt;. And you can cool off from the summer heat in Arendelle by riding the new &lt;em&gt;Frozen Ever After&lt;/em&gt; attraction in Norway and visiting with Anna &amp;amp; Elsa from &lt;em&gt;Frozen&lt;/em&gt; in the new Royal Sommerhus. Then head over to Disney’s Hollywood Studios to visit with the lovable snowman, Olaf!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Speaking of an awakening, &lt;em&gt;Star Wars&lt;/em&gt; fans will definitely want to visit the new Star Wars experiences in Disney’s Hollywood Studios. &lt;em&gt;Star Tours&lt;/em&gt; has been updated to include a visit to Jakku from &lt;em&gt;The Force Awakens&lt;/em&gt; (we’ve seen this and it’s awesome!). Then head over to the new &lt;em&gt;Star Wars Launch Bay&lt;/em&gt; to encounter Kylo Ren or visit with everyone’s favorite Wookiee, Chewbacca! There’s also a brand new stage show called &lt;em&gt;Star Wars: A Galaxy Far, Far Away&lt;/em&gt; that includes Darth Vader, Stormtroopers, Kylo Ren, R2-D2, C-3PO, Chewbacca, Darth Maul, Captain Phasma, and BB-8. Captain Phasma also leads a squad of Stormtroopers in the March of the First Order, several times per day. And you can end the day with &lt;em&gt;Star Wars: A Galactic Spectacular&lt;/em&gt;, a fireworks, laser, and projection show set to music from &lt;em&gt;Star Wars&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Disney’s Animal Kingdom will light up at night with &lt;em&gt;Rivers of Light&lt;/em&gt;, a new nighttime spectacular set on the Discovery River. &lt;em&gt;Kilimanjaro Safaris&lt;/em&gt; will go out for nighttime expeditions that will include new animals such as hyenas and African Wild Dogs. Music, dancing, food, and drinks can be found at &lt;em&gt;Discovery Island Carnivale&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Harambe Wildlife Parti&lt;/em&gt;, two new nighttime parties in the Animal Kingdom. Finally, the &lt;em&gt;Tree of Life&lt;/em&gt; will come alive with lights and colors several times per night.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Over at Blizzard Beach, Kristoff and Olaf will host the inaugural &lt;em&gt;Frozen Games&lt;/em&gt;, a cool competition in a water park that appears to have been overcome by a snowstorm. And in Disney Springs (formerly Downtown Disney), you can shop and dine at several new shops and restaurants.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;As you can see, there’s a lot of new stuff coming to Walt Disney World this summer! And to make your trip even more amazing, you can save up to 30% on your room at select resort hotels and receive a special "Awaken Summer" MagicBand featuring BB-8! If you’ve not planned a trip to Walt Disney World this summer, what are you waiting for? Contact Raymie at &lt;a href="mailto:raymie@simplymagicalvacations.com"&gt;raymie@simplymagicalvacations.com&lt;/a&gt; to awaken your summer at Walt Disney World!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;What new attraction or experience are you looking forward to the most at Walt Disney World this summer? Leave us a comment and let us know!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/04/05/Summer-Awakens-at-Walt-Disney-World.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Early Breakfast in Fantasyland</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/04/06/Early-Breakfast-in-Fantasyland.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/7DMT_Doc.jpg" alt="7DMT Doc.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;One of the biggest decisions you’ll make when planning a Disney World vacation is whether to eat a good breakfast before going to the parks or going straight to the parks to be the first in line for some of your favorite attractions. Now you can choose both if you take advantage of "Disney Early Morning Magic".&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;On select mornings from 7:45-10:00am, a very limited number of guests will be the first to enter the Magic Kingdom and Fantasyland. At &lt;em&gt;Pinocchio Village Haus&lt;/em&gt;, you can enjoy a breakfast that includes pastries, fruits, scrambled eggs, waffles, bacon, sausage, and much more. And before the crowds get too heavy, you’ll have quick access to &lt;em&gt;Peter Pan’s Flight&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Seven Dwarfs Mine Train&lt;/em&gt;, and &lt;em&gt;The Many Adventures of Winnie the Pooh&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;This special early morning access to Fantasyland will cost $69 for adults and $59 for children (ages 3-9) in addition to regular park admission. It appears that it will be offered on most Tuesday and Saturday mornings starting April 26th. If this is something you think you might want to try out, you can read more about it and check for availability by clicking &lt;a href="https://disneyworld.disney.go.com/dining/early-morning-magic"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;It’s important to understand that although this event runs from 7:45-10:00am, the Magic Kingdom still opens at 9:00am on those days. So participating guests will only have exclusive access to Fantasyland for an hour and 15 minutes (unless they plan to keep Fantasyland closed to regular guests until 10:00am—​which is unlikely). Therefore, we’re undecided if breakfast plus quick access to those three rides in such a short period of time justifies the $69/person price tag. In comparison, breakfast at &lt;em&gt;Cinderella’s Royal Table&lt;/em&gt; is roughly $60 for adults and $36 for children, which includes the experience of dining in the castle, albeit without quick access to 3 Fantasyland attractions.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;What do you think? Does "Disney Early Morning Magic" seem like something you’d want to try? Leave us a comment and let us know.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/04/06/Early-Breakfast-in-Fantasyland.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nighttime awakens at Disney's Animal Kingdom this summer</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/04/20/Nighttime-awakens-at-Disneys-Animal-Kingdom-this-summer.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/TreeOfLifeAwakens.jpg" alt="TreeOfLifeAwakens.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Yesterday, Disney invited members of the press and blogging/podcasting communities to go behind the construction walls at several of the new attractions and shows coming to Walt Disney World this summer. Unfortunately, MouseGuests was not invited (&lt;em&gt;Disney, if you’re reading this, please consider inviting us next time!&lt;/em&gt;), so we had to follow along from home on Twitter. Nevertheless, we have some updates on what is coming to Disney’s Animal Kingdom.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;As you may already know, &lt;em&gt;Rivers of Light&lt;/em&gt;, the new nighttime show on the Discovery River in Animal Kingdom, has been delayed. Although it was supposed to debut this Friday, technical problems have prompted Disney to delay the opening of the show. Rumor is that they’re having a difficult time with the GPS systems keeping the barges from crashing into each other in the currents of the Discovery River. At this time, it is unknown when &lt;em&gt;Rivers of Light&lt;/em&gt; will open.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Nevertheless, the setbacks on &lt;em&gt;Rivers of Light&lt;/em&gt; will not stop Disney from opening Animal Kingdom’s other new experiences, including &lt;em&gt;Discovery Island Carnivale&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Harambe Wildlife Parti&lt;/em&gt;, the new nighttime &lt;em&gt;Kilimanjaro Safaris&lt;/em&gt;, and &lt;em&gt;Tree of Life Nighttime Awakenings&lt;/em&gt;. In addition, Disney announced last night that while the glitches are being worked out with &lt;em&gt;Rivers of Light&lt;/em&gt;, an interim show, &lt;em&gt;Jungle Book: Alive with Magic&lt;/em&gt;, will be shown on the Discovery River nightly, featuring scenes from the hit live action &lt;em&gt;Jungle Book&lt;/em&gt; movie.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;(We’ve seen a few videos taken of the &lt;em&gt;Tree of Life Nighttime Awakenings&lt;/em&gt; from last night and it looks amazing.)&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Starting on Memorial Day Weekend, Animal Kingdom will be open until 8pm for guests to experience the park after dark. Additionally, the new &lt;em&gt;Tiffins&lt;/em&gt; restaurant will be open for lunch and dinner starting that same weekend.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Although we’re disappointed that &lt;em&gt;Rivers of Light&lt;/em&gt; and these new experiences won’t be available while we’re in Disney World at the end of this month, we’re excited about what’s coming to Disney’s Animal Kingdom. We’ll patiently wait for the kinks to be worked out with &lt;em&gt;Rivers of Light&lt;/em&gt; and be all the more anxious to see it on our next trip.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;What do you think of these new experiences coming to Disney’s Animal Kingdom? Leave a comment and let us know!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/04/20/Nighttime-awakens-at-Disneys-Animal-Kingdom-this-summer.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eat free at Disney World in 2016!</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/04/25/Eat-free-at-Disney-World-in-2016.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/TonysDessert.jpg" alt="TonysDessert.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Anyone who has ever been to Walt Disney World can tell you that if you leave feeling hungry, you’ve done something wrong. Disney World has some of the most amazing dining options you can find anywhere. Sure you can find burgers and turkey legs, staples of theme park dining. But there are many more choices to satisfy even the most critical palates, including several fine dining options.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;As if a trip to Walt Disney World isn’t magical enough, what if you could go and eat for free? Today Disney has announced free dining for select resorts and dates in 2016. All you need to do is book non-discounted 5-night/6-day package that includes a room at one of the participating Walt Disney World Resort hotels and tickets with the &lt;em&gt;Park Hopper&lt;/em&gt; or &lt;em&gt;Water Parks &amp;amp; More&lt;/em&gt; option.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The dates included in this offer are for arrivals most nights:&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="ulist"&gt; 
 &lt;ul&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;August 23 - October 1, 2016&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;November 15 - November 21, 2016&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;November 26 - November 28, 2016&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;December 10 - December 31, 2016&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;/ul&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;You must book your trip before July 8, 2016. But we don’t recommend you wait that long. Free Dining at Disney World is always incredibly popular and the limited rooms book up fast. Contact &lt;a href="mailto:raymie@simplymagicalvacations.com"&gt;raymie@simplymagicalvacations.com&lt;/a&gt; as soon as possible to plan your next trip and take advantage of this free dining offer!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/04/25/Eat-free-at-Disney-World-in-2016.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Walkin' Around the World</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/06/02/Walkin-Around-the-World.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/FoF_Goofy.jpg" alt="FoF Goofy.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Back in February, I shared our walking trip report for our December trip to Walt Disney World. I reported that on that 7 day trip, we walked over 68 miles and averaged 9.74 miles per day. Today, I want to update you on our most recent trip and take a look at how many miles we put in.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;This particular trip, April 29-May 3, was unique in the sense that Raymie was there for training purposes. This meant that for 2 days of our trip, it was mostly me and the girls exploring the parks without her. Given that she visited virtually every single Disney resort hotel on property, I’d wager that she put in a lot more miles than us. But I only have data for what I walked, taken from the Health app on my iPhone.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Here’s how we did:&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="ulist"&gt; 
 &lt;ul&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;Apr 29th - 8.95 miles : We arrived mid-day and all of us went straight to the Magic Kingdom. After having lunch at &lt;em&gt;Skipper Canteen&lt;/em&gt; (it was wonderful!), we hit as many attractions as we could. We ended up leaving just before park closing so we could catch a bus back to our resort (Port Orleans French Quarter) before the exiting crowds got too heavy.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;Apr 30th - 10.32 miles : On this day, it was just the girls and me for a mostly full day at Epcot. We walked all over Future World in the morning, had lunch at Akershus, and then took a relatively quick tour of World Showcase to see all of the Flower and Garden Festival topiaries. We ended our day at Epcot early because we wanted to see Yehaa Bob at Port Orleans Riverside. We met up with Raymie, headed back to our resort for dinner at Sassagoula Floatworks and then walked over to Port Orleans Riverside to see Yehaa Bob.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;May 1st - 8.02 miles : Again, Raymie was in training on this day, so me and the girls started our day in Animal Kingdom. We hit the highlights (&lt;em&gt;Festival of the Lion King&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Kilimanjaro Safari&lt;/em&gt;, etc) and had a quick lunch at &lt;em&gt;Pizzafari&lt;/em&gt;. Then we hopped over to the Magic Kingdom in time to see &lt;em&gt;Festival of Fantasy Parade&lt;/em&gt;, enjoy some attractions. We settled around the hub after dinner to stake out a spot for the &lt;em&gt;Main Street Electrical Parade&lt;/em&gt;. Raymie met us there and then we went back to the resort to rest just as &lt;em&gt;Wishes&lt;/em&gt; was starting.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;May 2nd - 6.05 miles : With the full family together for the day, we went to Disney’s Hollywood Studios, riding &lt;em&gt;Toy Story Midway Mania&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Star Tours&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Tower of Terror&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Rock 'n' Roller Coaster&lt;/em&gt;, and taking some time in &lt;em&gt;Star Wars Launch Bay&lt;/em&gt; to catch up with Kylo Ren and Chewbacca. We also caught a &lt;em&gt;Citizens of Hollywood&lt;/em&gt; show near the &lt;em&gt;Tower of Terror&lt;/em&gt; before getting dinner at Hollywood &amp;amp; Vine where we had reserved a table with the &lt;em&gt;Fantasmic!&lt;/em&gt; dinner package. Unfortunately, some very intense storms blew through the area and instead of seeing &lt;em&gt;Fantasmic!&lt;/em&gt; we were all huddled under the awning at the entrance of &lt;em&gt;50’s Prime Time Cafe&lt;/em&gt; until the rain blew over. After the rain let up, we stuck around for &lt;em&gt;Symphony in the Stars&lt;/em&gt; before heading back to the resort.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;May 3rd - 6.78 miles : On our last day, we started our day with breakfast at &lt;em&gt;'Ohana&lt;/em&gt;. Then we went back to the Magic Kingdom and hit as many attractions as could before having to leave for the airport.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;/ul&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;That’s a total of 40.12 miles over the five days. Our average miles per day for this trip was 8.024—​lower than our December trip. I attribute the difference to the heat and us turning in early on most evenings. It was also a shorter trip, with one day being spent at Hollywood Studios (a smaller park requiring less walking) and two other days being half-days at the Magic Kingdom.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;As before, I strongly recommend that you find comfortable shoes for your Disney vacation. Speaking for myself, I break a few common-sense rules and wear sandals. Generally, sandals are a poor choice for walking in Disney World or Disneyland, but for some reason my sandals (Teva Forebay) are more comfortable for me than most walking shoes. Raymie and the girls both like Skechers GOWalk. But what’s most important is that you find a shoe that is comfortable and fits right. And be sure to break it in by wearing it for at least a few weeks before your trip. I also recommend packing some moleskin, bandaids, and rub your feet down with an anti-friction stick every morning to avoid nasty blisters.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;We leave in two days for a weeklong trip to Disneyland. This will be our first Disneyland trip where I’ll track our miles. Stay tuned to this blog for a Disneyland walking report.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;How many miles have you logged on your Disney World or Disneyland trips? Have any tips on how to avoid blisters and aching feet? Leave a comment and let us know!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/06/02/Walkin-Around-the-World.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frozen Ever After opens in Epcot</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/06/23/Frozen-Ever-After-opens-in-Epcot.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/FrozenEverAfterDis.jpg" alt="FrozenEverAfterDis.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Earlier this week, &lt;em&gt;Frozen Ever After&lt;/em&gt; opened in Epcot’s Norway Pavilion. With the continued popularity of &lt;em&gt;Frozen&lt;/em&gt;, this new attraction was inundated with long lines of people waiting to see how the kingdom of Arendelle is represented in this new dark ride.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The standby lines extended past Epcot’s China Pavilion and had an expected wait time of over 5 hours. To make things worse, the ride went down several times during its first two days of operation, leaving guests waiting even longer to get in. To keep everyone cool, cast members were handing out free Mickey ice cream bars to those in line. As I write this, on the third day of operation, the posted standby lines are again at 300 minutes (although &lt;a href="https://touringplans.com/disney-world-app"&gt;TouringPlans.com’s "Lines" app&lt;/a&gt; suggests the actual wait might be 244 minutes).&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, we haven’t had an opportunity to ride &lt;em&gt;Frozen Ever After&lt;/em&gt; yet. That’s okay, though. We hope that by the time we visit Disney World later this year the lines will be shorter and the kinks will have been worked out. Even so, I’ve had a chance to view several of the on-ride videos that other guests have posted in the past couple of days and am rather impressed with what I’ve seen.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="admonitionblock warning"&gt; 
 &lt;table&gt; 
  &lt;tbody&gt;
   &lt;tr&gt; 
    &lt;td class="icon"&gt; &lt;i class="fa icon-warning" title="Warning"&gt;&lt;/i&gt; &lt;/td&gt; 
    &lt;td class="content"&gt; Spoilers follow! &lt;/td&gt; 
   &lt;/tr&gt; 
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
 &lt;/table&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Like its predecessor, &lt;em&gt;Maelstrom, _Frozen Ever After&lt;/em&gt; is a combination boat and dark ride. It follows almost the identical course as &lt;em&gt;Maelstrom&lt;/em&gt;, although the queue and loading area are now in what was previously a theater that showed a film about the history and culture of Norway. Instead of seeing Odin, vikings, polar bears, and oil derricks, &lt;em&gt;Frozen Ever After&lt;/em&gt; takes you on a brief tour of Arendelle and Elsa’s ice castle. Along the way, you’ll see Olaf, Sven, the rock trolls, Sven, Anna, Kristoff, Marshmallow, and Snowgies. And, of course, you’ll see Elsa in her ice castle.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The first thing I noticed about this attraction was how incredibly smooth and convincing the audio-animatronics are. Facial features are rear-projected, much like the faces of the Seven Dwarfs in the &lt;em&gt;Seven Dwarfs Mine Train&lt;/em&gt;. But what’s more impressive is how much range of motion many of the audio-animatronic characters have and how smoothly they move. Most notably, the Elsa figure in the ice castle is incredible. It’s as if she has been transported out of the movie and is standing in front of you.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;I also found it refreshing that this ride isn’t just an abridged retelling of the source story, like so many dark rides are. This is an all new story where Elsa is inviting everyone to her ice castle for a snowy summer celebration. Many of the popular songs from the movie are incorporated into the ride, although with new lyrics to fit the new story. The only song that seems unchanged is "Let it Go", which Elsa is singing in her ice castle.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;This is easily one of the best dark rides Disney has ever done, on par with &lt;em&gt;Seven Dwarfs Mine Train&lt;/em&gt; and approaching the quality of Hong Kong Disneyland’s &lt;em&gt;Mystic Manor&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The only disappointment I had in watching the videos for this attraction is that Marshmallow doesn’t feature more prominently. I had imagined a rather large Marshmallow animatronic with a huge range of motion, not entirely unlike what &lt;em&gt;Expedition Everest&lt;/em&gt;'s yeti was supposed to do. In fact, Harold, the abominable snowman in Disneyland’s &lt;em&gt;Matterhorn Bobsleds&lt;/em&gt; moves about more than Marshmallow does in &lt;em&gt;Frozen Ever After&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;I’m still unconvinced that a &lt;em&gt;Frozen&lt;/em&gt; ride is fitting for Epcot’s Norway Pavilion—​I think it’d have been a better fit for the Magic Kingdom. Even so, I’ll admit Epcot needs more popular attractions like this to appeal to the younger audience and to balance crowds away from Future World attractions like &lt;em&gt;Soarin'&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Test Track&lt;/em&gt;. But if a &lt;em&gt;Frozen&lt;/em&gt; attraction is going to be in Epcot, I’m glad that it is so well done.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;What do you think about &lt;em&gt;Frozen Ever After&lt;/em&gt;? Have you ridden it yet? Leave a comment and let’s discuss!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/06/23/Frozen-Ever-After-opens-in-Epcot.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disneyland by the mile: A walking trip report</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/06/24/Disneyland-by-the-mile-A-walking-trip-report.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/Soundsational_Genie.jpg" alt="Soundsational Genie.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/06/02/Walkin-Around-the-World.html"&gt;Last Month&lt;/a&gt; I shared a brief trip report on how many miles we logged while walking around Disney World in May. As promised then, I’m now following up on a similar report from our visit to Disneyland in June.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;On this trip, we went with some friends who have never been to Disneyland before. Because of that, we felt compelled to show them as much of Disneyland as we possibly could—​which, of course, meant a lot of walking.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Although similarly designed, Disneyland Park is quite a bit smaller than Disney World’s Magic Kingdom (85 acres vs. 107 acres). In spite of the small size, there’s a lot to do in both Disneyland and Disney California Adventure. And since the parks are relatively close to each other and close to all of the resort hotels, you find yourself walking a lot more than riding a bus or a monorail.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Here’s a brief rundown of each day of the trip:&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="ulist"&gt; 
 &lt;ul&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;June 4th - 4.48 miles : This was primarily a day of travel. We didn’t even leave home until lunchtime and our flight landed at LAX at around 4pm. We didn’t even bother going into the parks on this day. Instead, we walked around Downtown Disney and had dinner at &lt;em&gt;White Water Snacks&lt;/em&gt; in Disney’s Grand Californian Hotel &amp;amp; Spa. Even so, we put in nearly 5 miles worth of airport and Downtown Disney walking.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;June 5th - 9.38 miles : We always try to bookend our Disneyland trips in Disneyland Park. We entered the park at rope drop. After a few Fantasyland dark rides, the girls went to a Bibbidi Bobbidi Boutique appointment while the guys rode &lt;em&gt;Big Thunder Mountain&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Star Tours&lt;/em&gt;. We had lunch at Cafe Orleans (the Monte Cristo is amazing!) and made sure to catch &lt;em&gt;Mickey’s Soundsational Parade&lt;/em&gt; (as it’d be the only day it was running during our trip) and later saw &lt;em&gt;Paint the Night&lt;/em&gt;. Due to high winds, &lt;em&gt;Disneyland Forever&lt;/em&gt; was cancelled, so we’d have to see it on another night. Overall, we didn’t have a well-formed plan for this day, so we zig-zagged a lot, resulting in the high number of miles.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;June 6th - 9.33 miles : On our second day, we went to Disney California Adventure. We started early enough to ride &lt;em&gt;Radiator Springs Racers&lt;/em&gt; a couple of times in a row, before working our way counter-clockwise around the park, hitting Bugs Land and the &lt;em&gt;Tower of Terror&lt;/em&gt; (twice in a row) next. We met up with Nick Wilde and Judy Hopps in Hollywoodland. It was at this point we realized that there was no way we’d be able to see &lt;em&gt;Frozen-Live at the Hyperion&lt;/em&gt; on this day, so we continued our trek around the park. We left the park for a bit for dinner at &lt;em&gt;Goofy’s Kitchen&lt;/em&gt;, before returning to the Paradise Pier area for that evening’s showing of &lt;em&gt;World of Color-Celebrate!&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;June 7th - 8.96 miles : The next day found us again in Disney California Adventure. Most of the crew stayed in the Grizzly Peak Airfield area and rode &lt;em&gt;Soarin'&lt;/em&gt; (still the original at that time) while I stood in line to get Fastpasses for &lt;em&gt;Frozen-Live at the Hyperion&lt;/em&gt;. With Fastpasses in hand, I returned to ride &lt;em&gt;Soarin'&lt;/em&gt; myself and then we all went back to Hollywoodland to ride &lt;em&gt;Monsters, Inc. Mike and Sulley to the Rescue!&lt;/em&gt; before standing in an oppressively claustrophobic line to get into the Hyperion Theater. After seeing the new &lt;em&gt;Frozen&lt;/em&gt; show (which, was amazing and well worth seeing), we headed over to &lt;em&gt;Storyteller’s Cafe&lt;/em&gt; at the Grand Californian for lunch. After returning to the park, we rode as many Paradise Pier attractions as we could fit in, then ended our day with some ice cream from &lt;em&gt;Clarabelle’s&lt;/em&gt; and one more ride on &lt;em&gt;Radiator Springs Racers&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;June 8th - 8.34 miles : On our final day with our friends, we hit Disneyland Park once again. We rode the monorail into the park and rode &lt;em&gt;Matterhorn Bobsleds&lt;/em&gt; before breakfast at &lt;em&gt;Plaza Inn&lt;/em&gt; (hands-down the best character meal in either Disney World or Disneyland). Then set out to hit as many attractions as we could. We picked up Fastpasses for &lt;em&gt;Hyperspace Mountain&lt;/em&gt; and signed the kids up for &lt;em&gt;Jedi Training: Trials of the Temple&lt;/em&gt;. Then we headed to ToonTown, met Mickey Mouse at his house, rode &lt;em&gt;Gadget’s Go Coaster&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Roger Rabbit’s Car Toon Spin&lt;/em&gt;. Unfortunately, Jedi Training ended up being cancelled, but they made up for it by letting us walk right in to see Kylo Ren. And we visited (and hugged) Chewbacca while we were there. At some point, we waited in a very long line for Dole Whips and continued to ride as many rides as we could before saying goodbye to our friends in Downtown Disney.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;June 9th - 6.54 miles : The next day, Raymie woke up not feeling well, so we slept in before going to &lt;em&gt;Ariel’s Grotto&lt;/em&gt; for lunch. After lunch, Raymie went back to the hotel room while me and the girls explored Disney California Adventure by ourselves. Given that Madi isn’t much of a thrill-ride junkie, we stayed clear of &lt;em&gt;Tower of Terror&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;California Screamin'&lt;/em&gt; (and we had ridden them earlier in the week) and spent most of our day in Paradise Pier and Cars Land. We ended the day relatively early by riding &lt;em&gt;Soarin'&lt;/em&gt; again. Later, Maisy and I walked back over to Disneyland Park where we hid out in the &lt;em&gt;Main Street Cinema&lt;/em&gt; waiting for &lt;em&gt;Paint the Night&lt;/em&gt; to pass by so we could see &lt;em&gt;Disneyland Forever&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;June 10th - 3.76 miles : On our last day, we had planned to go to Disneyland Park, but Raymie still wasn’t feeling better and if we were to go, we’d need to buy a 1-day ticket (we had only bought a 5-day ticket for the first part of the week), so we decided to take it easy and walk around Downtown Disney for awhile. We had lunch at &lt;em&gt;Earl of Sandwich&lt;/em&gt; and then Maisy and I walked over to the Disneyland Hotel to look around and see the scale model of &lt;em&gt;Big Thunder Mountain&lt;/em&gt; in the lobby of the Frontier Tower. Then we waited in the lobby of the Grand Californian, hunted for hidden Mickeys, and finally boarding our bus back to LAX to go home. (Interesting note: We saw Dave Foley, the voice of &lt;em&gt;A Bug’s Life&lt;/em&gt;'s Flik and actor in a handful of TV shows) was outside about to check into the hotel as we were leaving.)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;/ul&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Note that all of these miles were reported by the built-in "Health" app on my iPhone 6S. I’ve found it to be relatively accurate, but other pedometers may have provided slightly different numbers. In short, your mileage may vary (pun intended).&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Crunching those numbers we get:&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="ulist"&gt; 
 &lt;ul&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;50.79 total miles walked during the trip; averaging 7.26 miles per day&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;42.55 miles walked on days we enter the parks; averaging 8.51 miles per day&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;17.72 miles walked on the two days spent in Disneyland Park; averaging 8.86 miles per day&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;24.83 miles walked on the three days spent in Disney California Adventure; averaging 8.28 miles per day&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;/ul&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Not surprisingly, our feet were sore and tired by the end of the trip. As usual, I wore my Teva sandals and they were fine for the most part. That last day in Disneyland Park (June 8th) my feet were in rather extreme pain by the end of the day, but I suspect that has more to do with the fact that I rarely sat down for most of the day and even then for only short breaks. My feet were much better the next day, however.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;That said, I am beginning to acknowledge that maybe I should try something other than sandals on our next trip. I’ve heard nothing but good things about shoes from &lt;a href="http://www.kurufootwear.com/"&gt;Kuru Footwear&lt;/a&gt;. Doing some self-diagnosis, prior to learning about Kuru, I think I might suffer from plantar fasciitis and Kuru claims to have shoes that help with that. Unfortunately, I have wide feet and their only shoes that measure wide aren’t currently in stock for my shoe size. But I hope to be able to give them a try on our next Disney trip.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;How many miles have you walked in Disney World or Disneyland? Do you have any tips on how to keep your feet comfortable when in the parks? Leave a comment and let us know!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disneyland</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 21:10:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/06/24/Disneyland-by-the-mile-A-walking-trip-report.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-28T21:10:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2016 Candlelight Processional narrator lineup and dinner packages announced</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/06/30/2016-Candlelight-Processional-narrator-lineup-and-dinner-packages-announced.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/Candlelight_AndyGarcia.jpg" alt="Candlelight AndyGarcia.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Disney has just announced the initial narrator lineup for this year’s Candlelight Processional, performed in the American Gardens Theater in Epcot. This year’s lineup includes:&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="ulist"&gt; 
 &lt;ul&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;11/25-27 – Steven Curtis Chapman&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;11/28-12/1 – Neil Patrick Harris&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;12/2-12/3 – Whoopi Goldberg&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;12/4-12/12 – TBA&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;12/13-12/15 – Meredith Vieira&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;12/16-12/18 – TBA&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;12/19-12/21 – Joe Morton&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;12/22-12/27 – TBA&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;12/28-12/30 – Cal Ripken, Jr.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;/ul&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;In addition to this news, dining packages which guarantee a seat for the Candlelight Processional are now available for breakfast, lunch, or dinner. These packages start at $27(adult)/$14(child) for breakfast and $47(adult)/$20(child) for lunch or dinner. Reservations for the dining packages can be booked via the My Disney Experience website or by calling 407-WDW-DINE. (Requires park admission, not included.)&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The Candlelight Processional is a popular annual event in Epcot during the holidays. Each night, a celebrity narrator tells the Christmas story along with a 50 piece orchestra and a choir performing Christmas carols. There are three performances per night.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;This year’s narrator lineup includes perennial favorites such as Steven Curtis Chapman, Neil Patrick Harris, and Whoopi Goldberg. We’ve personally seen the Candlelight Processional twice, once with Whoopi Goldberg as narrator and another time with Andy Garcia. It is a magnificent event and not to miss.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Have you had the opportunity to attend the Candlelight Processional in Epcot? Tell us about it by leaving a comment!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2016 13:51:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/06/30/2016-Candlelight-Processional-narrator-lineup-and-dinner-packages-announced.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-06-30T13:51:33Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Answers to our Disney World Independence Day trivia questions</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/07/04/Answers-to-our-Disney-World-Independence-Day-trivia-questions.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div id="preamble"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="sectionbody"&gt; 
  &lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
   &lt;p&gt;We hope you’ve had fun answering our Disney World Independence Day trivia questions today posted on &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/MouseGuests"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/mouseguests"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/mouseguests/"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;. As promised, here are the answers:&lt;/p&gt; 
  &lt;/div&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="sect1"&gt; 
 &lt;h2 id="_in_muppet_vision_3d_what_is_the_title_of_sam_eagle_s_glorious_3_hour_finale"&gt;In Muppet*Vision 3D, what is the title of Sam Eagle’s glorious 3 hour finale?&lt;/h2&gt; 
 &lt;div class="sectionbody"&gt; 
  &lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
   &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
    &lt;img src="/images/covers/4thTrivia5.png" alt="4thTrivia5.png"&gt; 
   &lt;/div&gt; 
  &lt;/div&gt; 
  &lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
   &lt;p&gt;In &lt;em&gt;Muppet*Vision 3D&lt;/em&gt;, Sam Eagle prepares a glorious 3 hour finale for the show called "A Salute to All Nations, but Mostly America". Unfortunately, Kermit the Frog informs him that he only has a minute and a half.&lt;/p&gt; 
  &lt;/div&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="sect1"&gt; 
 &lt;h2 id="_in_the_carousel_of_progress_who_are_john_and_sarah_going_to_the_lady_s_club_4th_of_july_celebration_as"&gt;In the Carousel of Progress, who are John and Sarah going to the lady’s club 4th of July celebration as?&lt;/h2&gt; 
 &lt;div class="sectionbody"&gt; 
  &lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
   &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
    &lt;img src="/images/covers/4thTrivia1.png" alt="4thTrivia1.png"&gt; 
   &lt;/div&gt; 
  &lt;/div&gt; 
  &lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
   &lt;p&gt;Sarah (the mother in &lt;em&gt;Carousel of Progress&lt;/em&gt;) is busy preparing her and John’s costumes for the lady’s club 4th of July celebration. They’ll be going as George and Martha Washington. John thinks he might be suited for the role, but thinks he’ll go next year as Benedict Arnold.&lt;/p&gt; 
  &lt;/div&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="sect1"&gt; 
 &lt;h2 id="_what_is_the_significance_of_the_building_number_on_the_hall_of_presidents"&gt;What is the significance of the building number on the Hall of Presidents?&lt;/h2&gt; 
 &lt;div class="sectionbody"&gt; 
  &lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
   &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
    &lt;img src="/images/covers/4thTrivia3.png" alt="4thTrivia3.png"&gt; 
   &lt;/div&gt; 
  &lt;/div&gt; 
  &lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
   &lt;p&gt;All of the buildings in Liberty Square have building numbers corresponding to years in U.S. history that they represent. At &lt;em&gt;The Hall of Presidents&lt;/em&gt;, the building number is 1787, which corresponds to the year that the U.S. Constitution was signed in Philadelphia.&lt;/p&gt; 
  &lt;/div&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="sect1"&gt; 
 &lt;h2 id="_what_words_appear_on_the_america_float_in_the_main_street_electrical_parade"&gt;What words appear on the America float in the Main Street Electrical Parade?&lt;/h2&gt; 
 &lt;div class="sectionbody"&gt; 
  &lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
   &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
    &lt;img src="/images/covers/4thTrivia4.jpg" alt="4thTrivia4.jpg"&gt; 
   &lt;/div&gt; 
  &lt;/div&gt; 
  &lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
   &lt;p&gt;The final and longest float in the &lt;em&gt;Main Street Electrical Parade&lt;/em&gt; is the America float which has a banner up front that says "To Honor America".&lt;/p&gt; 
  &lt;/div&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="sect1"&gt; 
 &lt;h2 id="_what_was_the_name_of_the_patriotic_group_that_once_played_woodwind_and_percussion_at_the_american_adventure_in_epcot"&gt;What was the name of the patriotic group that once played woodwind and percussion at the American Adventure in Epcot?&lt;/h2&gt; 
 &lt;div class="sectionbody"&gt; 
  &lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
   &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
    &lt;img src="/images/covers/4thTrivia6.png" alt="4thTrivia6.png"&gt; 
   &lt;/div&gt; 
  &lt;/div&gt; 
  &lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
   &lt;p&gt;Until September 2014, guests visiting the American Adventure pavilion in Epcot could enjoy performances by the Spirit of America Fife and Drum Corps. It’s our understanding that they were performing once again for a limited engagement today in Epcot.&lt;/p&gt; 
  &lt;/div&gt; 
  &lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
   &lt;p&gt;Notice the Hidden Mickey on the drum in the picture above.&lt;/p&gt; 
  &lt;/div&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="sect1"&gt; 
 &lt;h2 id="_in_the_carousel_of_progress_what_song_is_uncle_orville_humming_in_the_bath"&gt;In the Carousel of Progress, what song is Uncle Orville humming in the bath?&lt;/h2&gt; 
 &lt;div class="sectionbody"&gt; 
  &lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
   &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
    &lt;img src="/images/covers/4thTrivia2.png" alt="4thTrivia2.png"&gt; 
   &lt;/div&gt; 
  &lt;/div&gt; 
  &lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
   &lt;p&gt;In the Independence Day scene at the &lt;em&gt;Carousel of Progress&lt;/em&gt;, Uncle Orville gets no privacy. When he appears in the show, he’s reclined in the bathtub, humming "It’s a Grand Old Flag".&lt;/p&gt; 
  &lt;/div&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="sect1"&gt; 
 &lt;h2 id="_who_is_the_most_recent_u_s_president_to_be_represented_with_an_audio_animatronic_in_the_hall_of_presidents"&gt;Who is the most recent U.S. President to be represented with an audio-animatronic in the Hall of Presidents?&lt;/h2&gt; 
 &lt;div class="sectionbody"&gt; 
  &lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
   &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
    &lt;img src="/images/covers/4thTrivia7.png" alt="4thTrivia7.png"&gt; 
   &lt;/div&gt; 
  &lt;/div&gt; 
  &lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
   &lt;p&gt;This was kind of a trick question. Ever since &lt;em&gt;The Hall of Presidents&lt;/em&gt; opened in the Magic Kingdom in 1971, new audio-animatronic figures have been added as new presidents have taken office. And ever since Bill Clintion, the president taking office has recorded a speech for their audio-animatronic figure to present in the show. The most recent addition, therefore, is an audio-animatronic President Obama added in 2009.&lt;/p&gt; 
  &lt;/div&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2016 00:22:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/07/04/Answers-to-our-Disney-World-Independence-Day-trivia-questions.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-07-05T00:22:17Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Independency Day Trivia!</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/07/04/Independency-Day-Trivia.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/4thTrivia5.png" alt="4thTrivia5.png"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Happy 4th of July!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;When you visit Walt Disney World, it’s easy to find patriotic references to America. On this Independence Day, we decided it’d be fun to post a few trivia questions about some of those patriotic elements. Every hour or so, we’re going to post a trivia question on &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/MouseGuests"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/mouseguests"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/mouseguests/"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;. We’ll start with a fairly easy one and post it here on our blog as well. The first question is in the picture above: In Muppet*Vision 3D, what is the title of Sam Eagle’s glorious 3-hour finale?&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;For the remaining questions, you need to follow us on either &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/MouseGuests"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/mouseguests"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/mouseguests/"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;. Then later today, we’ll post the answers to all of the questions here on our blog. When you know the answer, please play along by posting it as a comment or reply.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Have a happy and safe 4th of July!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2016 13:41:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/07/04/Independency-Day-Trivia.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-07-04T13:41:37Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Parks live streaming every Monday in July</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/07/05/Disney-Parks-live-streaming-every-Monday-in-July.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/PaintTheNight.jpg" alt="PaintTheNight.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Did you watch the live stream of "Celebrate America!" last night on the Disney Parks Blog? Disney’s fireworks displays are amazing and their 4th of July spectacular was a dazzling example of how well Disney does pyrotechnics.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Last night’s live stream was just the first live stream on the Disney Parks Blog this month. Just before the show, they announced that there will be a live streaming event every Monday in July! The schedule for the rest of the month is as follows:&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="ulist"&gt; 
 &lt;ul&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;(July 11th) &lt;em&gt;Mickey’s Royal Friendship Faire&lt;/em&gt; - The new stage show that debuted last month at Cinderella Castle in the Magic Kingdom.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;(July 18th) &lt;em&gt;Star Wars: A Galactic Spectacular&lt;/em&gt; - This new nighttime show in Disney’s Hollywood Studios celebrates the entire Star Wars galaxy with fireworks, projections, and music.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;(July 25th) &lt;em&gt;Paint the Night&lt;/em&gt; - The dazzing electric parade from Disneyland that debuted as part of Disneyland’s Diamond Celebration last summer.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;/ul&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Even though we can’t go to Disney World and Disneyland as often as we’d like, it’s great to be able to experience the Disney Parks from home with these live streaming events. Stay tuned to MouseGuests.com and/or follow use on &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/MouseGuests"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/mouseguests"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; for more details on these events.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Did you tune in for the live streaming event last night? Are you planning to watch the other events this month? Which one are you most excited about? Leave a comment and let us know!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2016 14:54:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/07/05/Disney-Parks-live-streaming-every-Monday-in-July.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-07-05T14:54:19Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guardians of the Galaxy-Mission BREAKOUT! announced</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/07/24/Guardians-of-the-Galaxy-Mission-BREAKOUT-announced.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/GOTGExt600.jpg" alt="GOTGExt600.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Yesterday at San Diego Comic-Con, Kevin Feige, President of Marvel Studios, dropped the announcement (see what I did there?) that a new Guardians of the Galaxy attraction is coming to Disney California Adventure. The new attraction, named &lt;em&gt;Guardians of the Galaxy-Mission BREAKOUT!&lt;/em&gt;, is slated to open next summer.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Fans of the Marvel Universe will finally have an actual attraction in a Disney Park. Up until now, the Marvel presence in Disney’s U.S. parks has been limited to meet-n-greets and a display of Iron Man suits. Unfortunately, fans of the &lt;em&gt;Twilight Zone Tower of Terror&lt;/em&gt; will be disappointed to find out that the new &lt;em&gt;Guardians of the Galaxy&lt;/em&gt; attraction is a retheming of the 12 year old hotel to The Collector’s fortress.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The ride’s story will be that The Collector has captured the Guardians of the Galaxy andis displaying them in display cases suspended over an abyss. Rocket Raccoon has escaped and has recruited attraction guests to help rescue his colleagues.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The &lt;em&gt;Tower of Terror&lt;/em&gt;, as we currently know it, will close at the end of this year for work to begin on the retheming. Rumors are that this is just the first step in a bigger plan to rework the east side of Disney California Adventure to a new Marvel-themed land.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;My opinion: I’m not excited to hear that the &lt;em&gt;Tower of Terror&lt;/em&gt;'s existing theme is going away, but from what I’ve seen of the concept art, I’m hopeful that the new theme will be just as fun. And I think that the whole east side of Disney California Adventure is a thematic mess, so I hope that along with this retheming, the entire area can be reworked into a consistent Marvel theme.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;I’m also extremely happy that (as far as we know) the &lt;em&gt;Tower of Terror&lt;/em&gt; in Disney’s Hollywood Studios will remain untouched. Unlike DCA where the &lt;em&gt;Tower of Terror&lt;/em&gt; is just shoved in a corner, the DHS &lt;em&gt;Tower of Terror&lt;/em&gt; fits thematically perfect at the end of Sunset Boulevard. And, the ride experience of the east coast tower is far superior to that of the west coast tower. As long as the &lt;em&gt;Tower of Terror&lt;/em&gt; in Disney’s Hollywood Studios is left alone, I’m okay with whatever they want to do to its California counterpart.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;For what it’s worth, there are rumors circulating that there will be a &lt;em&gt;Guardians of the Galaxy&lt;/em&gt; attraction coming to Walt Disney World. But rather then retheme the &lt;em&gt;Tower of Terror&lt;/em&gt;, the Guardians will be part of an all new ride experience that will replace &lt;em&gt;Ellen’s Energy Adventure&lt;/em&gt; in Epcot. The jury’s still out on whether this makes sense or not or if it will even happen.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;What do you think about this news? Are you looking forward to more Marvel in Disney’s U.S. parks? Do you think this is a positive move for the &lt;em&gt;Tower of Terror&lt;/em&gt;? Leave a comment and let us know what you think.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>News</category>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2016 19:47:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/07/24/Guardians-of-the-Galaxy-Mission-BREAKOUT-announced.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-07-24T19:47:33Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disneyland's Paint the Night' live-stream tonight!</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/07/25/Disneylands-Paint-the-Night-live-stream-tonight.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/PTN_Mickey.jpg" alt="PTN Mickey.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;It has been an amazing July for Disney Parks fans who enjoy bringing Disney into their home. The &lt;a href="http://disneyparks.disney.go.com/blog/"&gt;Disney Parks Blog&lt;/a&gt; has been live-streaming every Monday, starting with &lt;em&gt;Celebrate America&lt;/em&gt; from the Magic Kingdom on July 4th. Then we watched &lt;em&gt;Mickey’s Royal Friendship Faire&lt;/em&gt; from the Magic Kingdom on July 11th. And just last week we tuned in to watch &lt;em&gt;Star Wars: A Galactic Spectacular&lt;/em&gt; from Disney’s Hollywood Studios.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Tonight, the Disney Parks Blog wraps up a month of live streaming with the dazzling &lt;em&gt;Paint the Night&lt;/em&gt; parade from Disneyland. You’ll definitely want to tune into the Disney Parks Blog tonight at 8:50pm PT (11:50pm ET) to see the show. The best way to view the parade is to use an HDMI adapter to hook your computer, tablet, or phone up to a larger television so that you can share the experience with friends and family.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;In case you’ve not seen &lt;em&gt;Paint the Night&lt;/em&gt; before, it is a modern take on a nighttime electrical parade, including 8 floats, 76 performers, and over 1.5 million LED lights. The soundtrack for the parade includes a blend of "Baroque Hoedown", Owl City’s "When Can I See You Again?", and several Disney classics. It’s a MUST-SEE parade (in our opinion, the best parade Disney has ever done)!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Who’s going to watch &lt;em&gt;Paint the Night&lt;/em&gt; tonight? What would you like to see live-streamed next on the Disney Parks Blog? Leave a comment and let us know!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disneyland</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2016 13:41:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/07/25/Disneylands-Paint-the-Night-live-stream-tonight.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-07-25T13:41:43Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Muppets Coming to the Magic Kingdom</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/07/28/Muppets-Coming-to-the-Magic-Kingdom.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/mkmuppets.jpg" alt="mkmuppets.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Starting in October, Sam Eagle, Kermit the Frog, Miss Piggy, and other Muppets can be found in the Magic Kingdom’s Liberty Square for a retelling of events in American history. &lt;em&gt;The Muppets Present…​Great Moments in American History&lt;/em&gt; will take place several times daily just outside of &lt;em&gt;The Hall of Presidents&lt;/em&gt; and will feature an original song along with the Muppets' own unique brand of humor.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Rumors about the Muppets appearing in Liberty Square started appearing over a month ago and some have noted some minor construction work in the windows near &lt;em&gt;The Hall of Presidents&lt;/em&gt; as evidence that something was about to happen. Now it is official. This new show will add some fun and activity to Liberty Square, which is often characterized as solemn and dull.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;What do you think about the Muppets coming to Liberty Square? Is it a welcome change? Or do you see it as a misfit? Leave a comment and let us know.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>News</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2016 14:28:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/07/28/Muppets-Coming-to-the-Magic-Kingdom.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-07-28T14:28:27Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Main Street Electrical Parade Returns to Disneyland</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/08/10/Main-Street-Electrical-Parade-Returns-to-Disneyland.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/MSEP_Mickey.jpg" alt="MSEP Mickey.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;After its most recent 6 year run in Disney World’s Magic Kingdom, the Main Street Electrical Parade will return to Disneyland for a limited engagement in early 2017!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Starting in Disneyland in 1972, the Main Street Electrical Parade has a long history of crossing the country, having rolled through the Magic Kingdom 3 times and once each for Disneyland and Disney California Adventure. It will close its current run in the Magic Kingdom on October 9th.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The Paint the Night Parade is Disneyland’s current nighttime light parade, debuting last summer for Disneyland’s 60th Anniversary Celebration. Paint the Night will go in hiatus, returning on select nights during the holiday season.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;It’s uncertain at this time what this means for a nighttime parade in the Magic Kingdom. Will a new parade start rolling through the Magic Kingdom soon? Or will Paint the Night cross the country early next year to become the Magic Kingdom’s nighttime parade?&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;What do you think about this shift in nighttime entertainment in both the Magic Kingdom and Disneyland? Leave a comment and let’s discuss!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disneyland</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2016 00:57:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/08/10/Main-Street-Electrical-Parade-Returns-to-Disneyland.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-08-11T00:57:09Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch the Main Street Electrical Parade Live!</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/08/25/Watch-the-Main-Street-Electrical-Parade-Live.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/MSEP_Tinkerbell.jpg" alt="MSEP Tinkerbell.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;As we’ve &lt;a href="http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/08/10/Main-Street-Electrical-Parade-Returns-to-Disneyland.html"&gt;reported before&lt;/a&gt;, the &lt;em&gt;Main Street Electrical Parade&lt;/em&gt; will be leaving Walt Disney World’s Magic Kingdom on October 9th to return home to Disneyland. Before it leaves the Magic Kingdom, however, there’s one more chance for all of us to watch it roll down Main Street U.S.A.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The Disney Parks Blog has &lt;a href="https://disneyparks.disney.go.com/blog/2016/08/inside-disney-parks-new-main-street-electrical-parade-povs-live-announcement/"&gt;just announced&lt;/a&gt; that they’ll be live-streaming the &lt;em&gt;Main Street Electrical Parade&lt;/em&gt; this Sunday night, August 28th, at 8:55pm Eastern. Mark your calendar and gather the family around to see the parade one last time before it glows away from the Magic Kingdom.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;What do you think? Are you excited to be able to see the &lt;em&gt;Main Street Electrical Parade&lt;/em&gt; one more time in the Magic Kingdom? Will you be watching? Leave us a comment and let us know!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2016 13:28:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/08/25/Watch-the-Main-Street-Electrical-Parade-Live.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-08-25T13:28:17Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jingle Bell, Jingle BAM!:New Nighttime Holiday Entertainment at Disney's Hollywood Studios</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/10/14/Jingle-Bell-Jingle-BAMNew-Nighttime-Holiday-Entertainment-at-Disneys-Hollywood-Studios.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;img src="/images/covers/JingleBoom.jpg" alt="JingleBoom.jpg"&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;After the switch for &lt;em&gt;Osborne Family Spectacle of Dancing Lights&lt;/em&gt; was turned off for the last time last year, it left many Disney World fans wondering what, if anything, Disney’s Hollywood Studios would offer for the 2016 holiday season.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Today we’ve learned that &lt;em&gt;Jingle Bell, Jingle BAM!&lt;/em&gt;, an all-new fireworks/projection show is debuting this holiday season. The premise of this show is that Santa Claus has gone missing and Wayne and Lanny, the elves from &lt;em&gt;Prep and Landing&lt;/em&gt; are leading the search. Holiday scenes featuring favorite Disney characters will be projected on the Chinese Theater while holiday music plays and fireworks light up the skies. And, of course, it wouldn’t be a Disney World holiday celebration without snow!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;From all appearances, this show uses the same projection technology as the popular &lt;em&gt;Star Wars: A Galactic Spectacular&lt;/em&gt;, which appears to be going on hiatus for the holiday season starting November 7th.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The first scheduled showing of &lt;em&gt;Jingle Bell, Jingle BAM!&lt;/em&gt; is for November 14th. For more information about &lt;em&gt;Jingle Bell, Jingle BAM!&lt;/em&gt; check out the announcement story on the &lt;a href="https://disneyparks.disney.go.com/blog/2016/10/all-new-holiday-nighttime-spectacular-jingle-bell-jingle-bam-coming-to-disneys-hollywood-studios-at-walt-disney-world-resort/"&gt;Disney Parks Blog&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Additionally, we also hear that Santa Claus himself may be hanging around Hollywood Studios this winter for meet and greet opportunities.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;What do you think of this new Christmas show at Disney’s Hollywood Studios? What holiday entertainment and activities do you look most forward to at Disney World? Leave a comment and let us know!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Disney World</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 13:38:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/10/14/Jingle-Bell-Jingle-BAMNew-Nighttime-Holiday-Entertainment-at-Disneys-Hollywood-Studios.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-10-14T13:38:26Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Progress City Primer</title>
      <link>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/10/18/Book-Review-Progress-City-Primer.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div class="imageblock"&gt; 
 &lt;div class="content"&gt; 
  &lt;a class="image" href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/0986205060/ref=as_li_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;creative=9325&amp;amp;creativeASIN=0986205060&amp;amp;linkCode=as2&amp;amp;tag=habumacom-20&amp;amp;linkId=bb1ea4f5992ed4690bbad1c892ec99a3"&gt;&lt;img src="/images/covers/ProgressCityPrimer.png" alt="ProgressCityPrimer.png"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; 
 &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;If you’re anything like me, you enjoy reading, but struggle to find books that both capture and hold your attention. As a Disney fanatic, however, I’ve discovered that there are countless books available about Walt Disney, the Walt Disney Company, and the Disney Parks. On the off-chance that some of our &lt;em&gt;MouseGuests&lt;/em&gt; readers are looking for a good book to read, I though I’d write some book reviews on this blog, sharing my thoughts on some of the best Disney books I find.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Among the many books on Disney are several books that delve into Disney history, including one that I finished recently, &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/0986205060/ref=as_li_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;creative=9325&amp;amp;creativeASIN=0986205060&amp;amp;linkCode=as2&amp;amp;tag=habumacom-20&amp;amp;linkId=bb1ea4f5992ed4690bbad1c892ec99a3"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Progress City Primer: Stories, Secrets, and Silliness from the Many Worlds of Walt Disney&lt;/em&gt; by Michael Crawford&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Walt Disney was a storyteller. And virtually everything that has the Disney name on it, from the movies to the theme parks, is wrapped in a story. So it seems fitting that there be a book that tells stories about Disney. That’s exactly what &lt;em&gt;Progress City Primer&lt;/em&gt; is: a collection of stories. Stories about Walt, stories about the imagineers, and stories about Disney’s Parks.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;The book doesn’t follow a serial flow. Instead, it is structured such that you can pick it up and start reading at any chapter. (I read it front to back, but that was merely by choice.) Although all of the stories are interesting and provide insight into Walt and the history of the Disney company, I rather enjoyed the stories about Walt himself near the beginning of the book the most. Some of the best stories are "The Lake Buena Vista STOLport", "Walt Disney vs. the Air Pirates", and "Pooh for President", all collected and retold brilliantly by the author. My favorite story in &lt;em&gt;Progress City Primer&lt;/em&gt; is a humorous story about Walt Disney, Herb Ryman, and 49 tiny elephants in "Walt’s Elephants". Although it’s one of the shortest (if not &lt;em&gt;the&lt;/em&gt; shortest) story in the book, this one story alone is worth the price of the book.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;I found &lt;em&gt;Progress City Primer&lt;/em&gt; difficult to put down and found myself in multi-chapter marathon reading sessions on airplanes as I travel. My only complaint is that after 33 fascinating stories, the book ended and I was wanting more Disney stories. As a parting gift, there is an appendix that collects several Disney-related recipes, including a recipe for the iconic strawberry shortcake from the &lt;em&gt;Hoop-Dee-Doo Musical Revue&lt;/em&gt; at Walt Disney World’s Fort Wilderness.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;I highly recommend &lt;em&gt;Progress City Primer&lt;/em&gt; to any reader who is even a marginal Disney fan. You won’t be disappointed.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="paragraph"&gt; 
 &lt;p&gt;Have you read &lt;em&gt;Progress City Primer&lt;/em&gt;? What did you think? What Disney books can you recommend? Leave a comment and let us know!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Reviews</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 15:36:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.mouseguests.com/2016/10/18/Book-Review-Progress-City-Primer.html</guid>
      <dc:date>2016-10-19T15:36:16Z</dc:date>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
